Wayne: Y’know I’m-I’m fed up.
I’m mad.
I’m—I don’t get it, I’m frustrated.
Why haven’t we figured this out yet?
Where do we begin?
You’d think we’d know, what ep-what episode
are we on?
Baaulp: Uh, this would be—
Trog: Two.
Baaulp: —episode…
Yeah, two.
Wayne: We’ve done two of these and we don’t
know!
Baaulp: Hold on, I can find the real number.
It is episode eighteen.
Wayne: This is episode eighteen, and I’m
Wayne.
Trog: I’m Trog.
Log: And I’m Log.
Baaulp: I’m Baaulp.
Gir: And I’m Gir.
Wayne: How does it feel to be eighteen, guys?
We can smoke cigarettes now!
Yeah!
Baaulp: No, we can’t.
Gir: No, it’s—
Wayne: Gir, you got that lighter?
Gir: No, the age got bumped to twenty-one.
Wayne: Did it?
Oh, it did!
Gir: It did, yeah [laughs].
Log: When did that happen?
Wayne: Yes!
Score for healthy lungs, fuck yeah.
Log: That’s weird.
Gir: Is it?
Log: I don’t know.
Wayne: Is that countrywide?
Gir: It’s countrywide, yes.
It’s a national law.
Wayne: Shit.
Log: How did we pick twenty-one?
Trog: Y’know, I’ve thought about that,
and I don’t have an answer.
Wayne: It’s your brain.
Isn’t it—that’s like, that’s when
the brain is considered mostly developed.
Baaulp: I don’t know, that’s a—
Gir: It is, yeah.
That’s the average age of when the brain
finishes development.
Wayne: I think that’s actually not true,
though, I believe it goes up to like, twenty-five.
Trog: Yeah, there’s no way that’s accurate.
Baaulp: I heard that there was research that
said like, you reach your peak mentally—not
physically, mentally—at thirty-five.
So, I actually can’t wait, I got like, I’m
about to like, my brain is about to go into
overdrive.
Log: Alright, no smoking, no drinking, we
have a decade left.
[Baaulp laughs]
Gir: Uh, I can already tell I’ve peaked
mentally.
Baaulp: Aw, come on.
Wayne: I am definitely on the downswing.
Trog: I’m twenty-seven, and whenever I think
back to me at twenty-one I’m like, “There’s
no way that my brain was fully developed when
I was twenty-one years old,” like—
Baaulp: Yeah, that’s what I—same.
Same.
Wayne: I misspoke, and I think what it’s
more-what it’s moreso is that your brain
has developed enough that the-the effects
of alcohol and cigarettes should not—note
the word should—should not do lasting damage.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Wayne: And that’s how they do it.
Gir: It’s not like mentally develop, it’s
physically—like your brains not physically
getting any larger, that’s what it is.
Trog: Speak for yourself.
Wayne: [Laughs] I don’t know…
Gir: You’re still stupid.
You’re still stupid and you’re still learning,
but your brain’s not getting much bigger.
Wayne: I bet we’re all wrong.
I bet there’s someone here—there’s a
fuckin’ craniologist in here listenin’
to this podcast—
Baaulp: Screaming.
They’re listening to this podcast in their
office and they’re screaming, they’re
like, throwing shit around like, “I can’t
believe these idiots, they’re so stupid.”
[Wayne laughs]
Gir: Send me an email if you think we’re
wrong, and I’ll uh, tell you to fuck off.
Baaulp: [Laughs] Wow, okay.
Trog: Oh, alright.
[Gir laughs]
Trog: I don’t even look at the emails, so…
Baaulp: This person—this person’s an intelligent
listener, this hypothetical listener’s very
intelligent, a valuable member—
Log: Thirty-five years old?
Baaulp: Yeah.
Like why are you gonna tell them to fuck off?
Log: Thirty-five years old, their brain has
grown to its peak.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Log: Now it’s gonna shrink.
It’s gonna shrink after they send the email,
so have some respect.
Gir: How are you gonna tell me I’m wrong?
You’re in decline, fucker.
Log: What are you talking about?
I’m on the rise.
Gir: [Crosstalk] I don’t know—Not you.
Log: Who’s thirty-five?
Gir: The hypothetical person.
Wayne: I think—Listen, listen, I think like,
my life is on the upswing, things are gettin’
better, they’re always getting better, but
I think my brain is absolutely on the downswing.
It is absolutely decaying day by day.
Every video game I play I lose like .5 IQ.
Gir: Hmm.
Log: I don’t know, you said Spookstablost
like four years ago, so it’s only up from
there.
Wayne: Yesterday-yester—No, yesterday I
tried to tell Scorpy that I needed to rerecord
like, a consent line for the voice changer—the
voice synthesis thing we’ve been using,
and I was like, not thinking, and I said,
“Yeah, I’ve gotta rerecord the….
Fat… fart…”
I didn’t mean to say that.
[Baaulp laughs]
Gir: Let me, let me help you out, ‘cause
I was also there.
Baaulp: Oh, man.
Gir: You said, “I have to rerecord the fat
fart,” you meant to say, “the first part,”
and your brain just went on a completely different
path.
Wayne, laughing: Yeah!
Gir: Your brain was like, “F…fuh…f-haha,
fat fart.”
Trog: I don’t understand though, Wayne,
I mean, you are playing Brain Age every day,
right?
Wayne: No?
Baaulp: Oh yeah, that’s a-that’s a—Yeah,
that’s what me and Trog are doin’.
Trog: That’s important.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Wayne: I’ve been letting the doctor down.
Trog: I mean, I don’t think I’ve never
not played Brain Age every single day since
it came out and now I’m in Mensa.
Baaulp: I play every day.
Wayne: What’s your brain age?
Trog: …Two.
Baaulp: Yeah.
I’m three.
Wayne: I think it’s supposed to be higher
at this point.
Trog: No, it’s ‘cause the lower the better.
Baaulp: What?
No, it’s like golf.
You want it lower.
Trog: Yeah, it’s like golf scores.
Wayne: Every time I ask you for a number in
this podcast, Trog, are you just gonna say
two?
‘Cause you’re on a roll right now.
Trog: It’s the funniest number I have.
Wayne, singing: [In the tune of “One is
the Loneliest Number”] Two is the funniest
number since the number one!
Log: We asked you to write the answers to
these math problems and you drew pictures
with childlike wonder.
[Wayne laughs]
Log: I think your brain is very young.
[Trog and Wayne laugh]
Wayne: Wonder and merriment.
Gir: Wonder and joy.
[Baaulp laughs]
Wayne: We asked Trog to recount the quadratic
formula and received a picture of a car with
two wheels.
[Baaulp and Wayne laugh]
Trog: Is that not just a bicycle or a motorcycle?
Gir: You can have only two wheels on a car,
it’s called not putting all four on.
Trog: I guess, I mean you wouldn’t go very
fast.
Wayne: That is the go-to way—That is the
go-to way for a kid to draw a car, like they
don’t consider that you would need to see—
Trog: Yeah.
Like a side profile.
Wayne: Yeah.
Like a 2D profile, like a bisected car, where
you see just the two wheels.
Gir: Uh-huh.
Wayne: Y’know, I specifically remember being
a kid and like, drawing all my shit like that
and like, drawing animals with just the two
little legs, and then learning like, “Oh,
if you draw like—If you draw like—at the
bottom of the animal you just draw the two
legs coming from behind, that you can depict
a slight perspective in a 2D space,” and
it like, blew my mind.
And then all my creatures had four legs.
Trog: Oh, hell yeah.
Wayne: And I was like, “Yeah.”
Baaulp: Even snakes.
[Wayne laughs]
Gir: That reminds me, the first time-the first
time as a child, like, when I’m in like
a art class at school or something and I like
finally got—grasped the concept of what
perspective is, I drew like a really nice
hallway, never once have I drawn perspective
that well again [laughs].
I had that flash and then it was just gone.
Wayne: Gir’s art magnum opus.
It happened early.
Log: You cleared the dark ages at age six.
Trog: Yeah.
[Wayne laughs]
Gir: Yeah, no, that’s exactly how Da Vinci
felt and then it’s just gone.
Wayne: I mean, you just drew that like, happy
emote like a week ago, and that was great.
I think you’ve resurfaced.
Gir: Ehh, true.
Baaulp: Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Log just referred to like, that period when
you’re a dumb kid as the dark ages.
Gir: It is!
Wayne: No!
He’s talking about the artistic dark ages.
Trog: Yeah.
Log: Yeah, I was referring to the time period
between the fall of the Roman empire—
Baaulp: Oh.
Wayne: Pre-Renaissance.
Log: —and the Renaissance era where people
just collectively forgot 3 dimensions and
perspective and the fact that humans are not
the same size as buildings.
[Wayne laughs]
Baaulp: Jokes on you ‘cause now I can—that’s
my idea.
Growing up is now called the little dark ages.
[Log laughs]
Wayne: Little dark ages.
That’s when they forgot that dogs didn’t
have human faces.
Log: Some artists still don’t know.
Wayne: What happened?
The dark ages couldn’t have been that bad,
that they forgot all that shit.
Log: They forgot everything!
Wayne, laughing: Oh, man.
Baaulp: You have to think of like-you have
to think like—Like, okay, ‘cause what
happened was, I mean you can look up the history
books, I-I think it would be too long to explain
how they got to the dark ages, but you have
to think about the scenario, which is like,
“Oh, shit, like, we have no more books anymore,
like the things that we all wrote down to
remember all those good shit—”
Wayne: Shit got destroyed.
Baaulp: —Yeah, “It’s all gone.”
Wayne: I know the history, it’s just a crazy
thing to fathom, like, so much—For a second
dark ages to happen, imagine that.
The fuckin’ Internet would have to be wiped,
the fuckin’—
Baaulp: The way I see it is like, okay, imagine
if the Internet just went away.
Like you rely-we all rely on the Internet
so much nowadays, imagine if it went away,
everybody would be just fuckin’ winging
it.
Because society has to go on, what are you
gonna do?
Not grow food?
Not eat?
But it’s like, “Oh shit, I have to do-I
have a presentation for this-for my job tomorrow,
well, I no longer have PowerPoint, I no
longer have Internet, all the records for
y’know, the sales for all of last year are
gone, I’m-I’m reduced to like scrawling
on a chalk board tellin’ my-the CEO like,
uh, I think it was good last year.”
Log: Yeah, the Internet went away but com-that
means computers don’t work anymore, the
Internet is gone.
You can’t use programs anymore.
Wayne: I try to log onto Twitter only to receive
an error that the entire Internet has been
disconnected.
I immediately start to cry and draw a human
with the face of a muttonchop.
[Baaulp laughs]
Log: I think a medieval peasant’s brain
would probably would’ve peaked like five
hundred years in the past, so they shouldn’t
have ever drank or smoked.
Gir: They smoked uh, little bit crazier shit
than we smoke.
Baaulp: Yeah, like crystals.
Wayne: God, I hope whenever we get like, proper
cloning tech going we use that to bring back
like, revive a bunch of peasants and like,
fuck with them.
That’d be awesome.
[Baaulp laughs]
Gir: I think there should be like a high school.
Trog: Now where are you going to get this
peasant DNA from?
Wayne: I wanna show them like, CGI of like,
dragons.
And like, put them in VR with a dragon in
front of them.
Baaulp: [Laughs] Wait, wait, wait, they-what
do you-what do you mean peasant DNA?
That’s our DNA you’re just—[Laughs].
Wayne: [Laughs] No, go find their bones!
You gotta go find their bones, pull their
bones out of the ground, and [laughs].
Trog: Would you be able to recognize a peasant’s
bones, though?
Like, “Oh, these bones look poor.”
Wayne: Yes!
He’d have the-he’d have the-they-it would
be in like a thatched roof cottage, and it
would have like a burlap sack on it’s head,
and like [laughs].
[Log, Trog, and Baaulp laugh]
Log: It’d be a perfectly preserved skeleton
eating just—
Gir: Bread.
Log: Gruel.
Trog: Eating a mutton.
Log: Holding a-holding a fossilized bowl of
gruel.
Trog: Yeah.
[Wayne and Baaulp laugh]
Wayne: Have a pitchfork.
Trog: Can’t wait till we can clown our own
serf.
[Wayne laughs]
Log: I think we should revive a medieval knight
and ask them about the giant snails that they
fought.
Wayne: Oh, man.
Baaulp: Y’know-y’know, you’re interested
in that era of time, I’m interested in the
seventies, I want—One day we’re gonna
be able to harvest hippie DNA and revive a
hippie and ask it about Woodstock.
[Wayne laughs]
Gir, laughing: Hippie DNA?
Log: Yeah, how come we haven’t revived a
hippie yet?
[Baaulp laughs]
Trog: Yeah, what happened to all those guys?
Wayne: We gotta go to like, ground zero for
Woodstock and like, dig up one of the bodies.
Log: How come we never revived a scene kid?
[Baaulp and Wayne laugh]
Trog: Same good question.
Wayne: Well, they still walk the earth, so
do the hippies!
We’re not at the point where we have to
do this, come like—When we’re still alive
like fifty years later, we can-then we can
look for the scene kids and the hippies.
Gir: I don’t think we should revive hippies,
they’re the reason the Beatniks went extinct.
Trog: Damn.
Baaulp: Oh, no.
No, you’re right.
Trog: Yeah, we’d be introducing an invasive
species.
Gir: Yeah.
[Wayne and Gir laugh]
Trog: A little dangerous.
Gir: Evolution culled them for a reason.
Trog: Yeah, we’re playing God at that point.
Wayne: We weren’t playing God at reviving
peasants?
Trog: No, who cares.
[Gir laughs]
Wayne: That one was a—[Laughs] Who gives
a shit?
Baaulp: I think the element that you’re
forgetting is that back then—and this is
like the dumbest thing ever, like I don’t
know how like—I would love to ask a historian.
Yo, if you’re a historian and you listen
to this and you know about this era of time,
please let us know, ‘cause I’m dying to
know this question.
So, they didn’t know that boiling water
made it safe to drink.
They didn’t figure that out, but they were
like, “Oh, if you cook with water like,
boil it, or if you make beer with water that’s
safe, so what do we drink?
Uh, let’s just drink beer all the time instead
of water.
All the time.”
And so, like, I think that adds—
Wayne: Is that really the order?
That they figured that out?
Baaulp: I’m pretty sure, yeah!
Wayne: I-I don’t know.
I feel like they figured out boiling water
made it safe pretty early, I’m not sure.
Baaulp: No, no, no—
Gir: No, boiling water came later, for sure.
Yeah.
Baaulp: Not in Europe at least, I don’t
know about the rest of the world, but not
in Europe.
Wayne: Damn, damn.
No wonder.
No fuckin’ wonder.
Log: They might not even have known that drinking
beer was safe—
Gir: No, they knew.
[Baaulp laughs]
Log: —they just did it and the ones that
drank beer didn’t die so they kept doing
it.
Wayne: Well they’d get drunk and like, forget.
Gir: That’s how they knew it was safe.
It was like, “Oh, well this—this fucked
up funny drink is the one that’s not killing
everyone, let’s just keep drinking that.”
Baaulp: Yeah.
Log: How would they be aware of that happening
around them, though?
They drink their beer, they’re not gonna
know all the water drinkers died.
Gir: Trial and error.
Log: They-they didn’t even know what a dog’s
face looked like.
Gir: Trial and error!
Wayne: [Laughs] They didn’t even know how
tall a building was!
They thought if you saw a building from a
hundred feet away it was about the size of
a man!
Baaulp: Oh my god, we put two and two together!
No wonder they drew like that!
They were all sloshed all the time!
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: I feel like there are going to be historians
listening to this podcast and getting really
upset.
[Baaulp laughs]
Gir: There were like six hundred years of
like, trial and error on basically everything.
That’s how we ended up with cheese.
Wayne: Yeah, like the trial and error of any
element of cooking is like, insane to me.
Gir: Yeah.
Wayne: Like imagine to be the first person
to make-to cook a loaf of bread.
Like, you would have lost your shit.
Gir: [Laughs] The steps-the steps it takes
to make bread—
Wayne: You would have been hailed as a fucking
god if you were the first man to make a bread.
Log: There is no trial there, like-there was
no trial, it was just error and then happy.
Baaulp: Yeah.
[Baaulp and Wayne laugh]
Wayne: Error and happy.
Trog: Yeah, they just accidentally let this
bacteria on this gruel.
Wayne: We have a lot of trial and error video
games, like Dark Souls and what not, when
are we gonna get a error and happy video game?
[Baaulp laughs]
Log: That is the history of it, right?
Like—
Gir: It’s GMod.
Log: —a medieval peasant just pulled a MasterGir
and left wheat and water or something, and
just—
Trog: And tried to microwave it.
Log: Through sheer error it turned into bread.
Gir: And they tried-they microwaved it.
Log: Or-or-or a bread-like substance.
Wayne: But here’s the thing.
That peasant makes that mistake and does that,
and he gets his-and he gets his accident bread,
but then he has to figure out why the fuck
that happened and how he recreates it, and
like—
Baaulp: I don’t think they’d care, I think
they’d just immediately make more because
bread’s the best thing they’ve ever had
in their entire life!
Wayne: They just keep leaving out their bread
jank in bottles and gettin’ this awful,
awful bread.
Baaulp: Yeah!
Eventually they get the process down pat.
Y’know, maybe when they sober up and-after
they dehydrate and sober up just a little,
y’know?
Log: So, you get down to it, it’s error
and trial.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Yeah, basically.
Wayne: Fuck that.
Same shit.
Fuck you.
Gir: There’s been so many things throughout
human history where, “I wanted to make X,
but I got Y instead, but Y’s pretty good,
too.”
Baaulp: Think about it like this.
If I had to wager a guess, uh, pasta as we
know it probably had its origins start as
fucked up balls of dough and water.
They were like, “Hey!
You fucked up making your fucked-up doughball
water soup thing!
What—Oh, this is pretty good.
And it’s in a pleasing shape, let’s do
this instead!”
[Gir laughs]
Trog: How they invented penne.
Baaulp: [Laughs] Yeah!
But that’s so depressing to think about.
Gir: Hey, you fucked up making these Alpha-BIts,
it’s all O’s!
Hey, I have an idea.
Baaulp: Ohhh, ohhhh.
Gir: Let’s call ‘em—
Wayne: Gir, they didn’t even have the alphabet,
then.
Gir, laughing: They make me-they make me cheery!
Wayne: Pasta came before the alphabet.
Log: I like to imagine the accidental creation
of traditional Korean noodles, where they
just accidentally seesawed on some bread for
an hour.
[Wayne and Baaulp laugh]
Baaulp: Now the real brain genius is the person
who thought about eating spicy food.
“Oh, this hurt me!”
Gir: “I like it!”
Baaulp: “I’m gonna—Yeah, I want some
more.”
Wayne: I would love to tap into the mental
process of the first person to eat a really
spicy food.
Like, I mean, I think it’s more-it’s less
like, “Oh, this hurt me, but I like it!”
and more like, “Oh, this hurt me, but I’m
not hungry anymore and I feel fine, I’m
not like, I don’t have dysentery, I’m
not like, experiencing awful death diarrhea
from eating this pepper.”
Baaulp: [Laughs] “I feel the vitamins rushing
through my body, ‘cause this is the most
nutritious thing I’ve had in a week!”
Gir: That’s the thing, is your body can
tell there’s nutrients in there, so if it’s
not so hot that it like, makes you scream,
then you’re probably just gonna eat it,
anyway.
Wayne: No, now I’m imagining the first peasant
to eat a pepper just takes a bite and just,
“AAAUUUGHH!
EEUUH!”
Gir, in a nasally voice: “Aaahhhh!”
Baaulp: Y’know how like, if you’ve never
had a lot of spicy food before, and you eat
something even mildly spicy, it’s like really
hot to you?
Imagine you’re the first person to eat this
ever and it’s spicy [laughs].
Trog: Probably scary.
Wayne: The first person to experience capsaicin
on their tongue probably thought they were
dying.
[Baaulp laughs]
Gir: They didn’t know ‘cause they had
a fuckin’ early primate brain.
Baaulp: “Aaaahhh, a shaman cursed this berry!”
Wayne: Are you-are you telling me they didn’t
know what death was?
Which I mean, like, I guess, maybe.
Gir: No, they had a monkey brain and went,
“Ooh, pain bad, me no like pain.”
Wayne: “This pepper’s so hot I’m going
to sleep forever!
I don’t know what that is!”
[Trog, Gir, and Wayne laugh]
Log: The first Homo erectus emerged from the
primordial pool and immediately ate a jalapeno.
[Everyone laughs]
Gir: He just stands up and looks around.
Wayne: The first one to slither out of the
goop.
There’s a single pepper waiting for it!
Baaulp: “AAAAHHHH.
AN EVIL-AN EVIL NAUTILUS CURSED THIS BERRY!”
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: That’s like a time traveler prank.
Wayne, laughing: The time traveler’s prank!
Trog: The time traveler prank is, go back
in time to the first, uh, creature that could
walk upright and give it a pepper.
Just see what happens.
Wayne: [Laughs] Then you go-then you go back
to the modern time and humanity does not exist,
you literally fucked up the timeline that
bad.
Trog: Yeah, you ruined the time stream.
Wayne: One pepper’s all it takes.
Log: Well, when you think about how we like,
are now breeding the stuff for enhanced spiciness
and stuff, like you could just go back and
kill a serf with a Caroline Reaper.
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: [Laughs] You give a serf a ghost pepper.
Trog: Those-I mean, those are basically weaponized
food, so.
Probably.
Baaulp: I have the opposite-I have the opposite
opinion.
I think it wouldn’t phase them at all because
if you like—One of my favorite things to
look at, like if I want a historical goof,
y’know, just laugh at some dumb people who
are already dead, what are they gonna do?
Beat me up?
I’m not going to heaven [laughs].
Trog: What?
Baaulp: Uh, [laughs]—
Gir: Okay.
[Wayne laughs]
Baaulp: Is to look up-is to look up Black
Plague cures, uh, this is the expensive cure.
Just buy emeralds, grind them up, and just
huff it.
Just like, throw-put emerald dust in a bag
and just huff that shit.
So I don’t think—I think it would hurt
them, I think we would get a reaction out
of them, but they’d be like, “Oh, this
really made me feel hot, like when I have
a fever.
Maybe this will cure the Black Plague!”
[Wayne laughs]
Gir: That’s the thing, is you can give some
like, poor serf uh, like a Carolina Reaper
and be like, “Hey, the more this hurts,
the less plague you have in you!
So just eat as many as you can, buddy!”
Baaulp: Yeah.
Wayne: What was a-what was a really—like,
name a really despicable monarch.
Trog: Um, you’re asking questions I’m
not prepared to answer.
Gir: Uh, Vlad the Impaler?
Baaulp: Yeah.
Wayne: No, not Vlad the Impaler.
Like—Oh, whatever.
Trog: I don’t know shit about history, my
man.
Baaulp: Yeah, I don’t know enough about
monarchs.
Wayne: Go—Okay, Queen Elizabeth, I don’t
know if she was good or bad, but we’re gonna
do this prank on her either way.
Trog, laughing: I don’t think she was that
bad, but I don’t know.
[Baaulp laughs]
Gir: The one that’s still alive?
The one that’s currently in the fucking
castle?
Wayne: [Laughs] No, not her!
No, no, not her!
Baaulp: Yeah, her.
Her!
Wayne: I’m not about to do this to her!
What I was gonna say is you go back in time,
go to some like, fucked up monarch, and dress
in like velvet robes and like, get gold lacing
and bring them a bong with a ghost pepper
in it and tell them to smoke it.
And tell them this will get them into heaven
for sure.
[Baaulp and Trog laugh]
Wayne: “I’m an angel, smoke this shit!”
Baaulp: “Yo bitch, I got your mandate sent
from heaven right here!”
Gir: Nah, I think it’s funnier to imagine
doing that to the current Queen.
Wayne: I guess you could do that to the current
Queen, she’s old enough, she’d fall for
it.
Gir: [In an old woman voice] “Okay!”
[Sucking sound, followed by old woman coughing]
[Wayne laughs]
Wayne: “Wow, an angel!”
[Baaulp laughs]
Wayne: And then she’d keep rippin’ it,
she’d Bogart that shit.
Gir: That would kill her.
That legitimately would kill her [laughs].
Trog: I think it’d make her stronger.
I think she would be too powerful; we’d
have to—
Wayne: [In a British accent] “The Queen
is Bogarting the bong!”
Baaulp: Hey, I wanna-I wanna—
Wayne: [In a British accent] “I say!”
Baaulp: Maybe it’s not the best to like,
hedge your bets but like, but I want to say,
best opening we’ve had so far to a podcast
[laughs]!
Wayne: [Laughs] I don’t know.
Trog: We are far past opening, this is-we’re
in the thick of it.
This is what we call the rising action of
the podcast.
Wayne: This is a main topic!
The whole time that we’ve been talking,
I’ve been staring at that fucking balloon
blast picture from last time.
Baaulp: Oh my god.
Trog: Why did we choose that?
Why did you choose that?
I’m pretty sure that was you.
Wayne: I found it and I thought it was great.
Trog: Alright.
Asked and answered.
Baaulp: Hey, it’s the thumbnail to the last
uh, last episode’s podcast, so—
Wayne: Y’know what, let’s make it the
thumbnail to this one, too.
Gir: That totally won’t be confusing!
Baaulp: I don’t know about that!
[Wayne laughs]
Baaulp: I don’t know.
Wayne: I think it’s a great gag.
I think that’s the best gag.
Baaulp: I don’t know, I don’t know…
Log: Yeah, just change the entire podcast
to be called Balloon Blast.
[Trog and Baaulp laugh]
Wayne: Just-just mirror it!
Flip it!
Just flip it the other way!
Baaulp, laughing: Just flip it!
Gir: Just put a giant red 2 in the middle
of the image.
Wayne: Then it’ll be Tsalb Noollab.
Gir: Awesome.
Trog: Well, you have any other terrible ideas
to ruin our podcast?
Or should we move onto a new topic?
Wayne: I mean, it’s a great idea.
Baaulp: What have we been playing?
What have we been playing?
Wayne: Video games?
Baaulp: What have we been jamming out to,
anything!
Watchin’, playing, readin’…
Rippin’!
Wayne: I’ve been playing badminton and rugby.
Baaulp: Oh, oh boy.
Trog: By yourself?
Wayne: Yeah, in my room.
Gir: You can do badminton by yourself.
Baaulp: Hey, hey, I got this pepper, you wanna
eat it?
[Trog and Wayne laugh]
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: You wanna play pepper, bro?
[Baaulp and Wayne laugh]
Gir: Play pepper.
Wayne, laughing: You wanna play peppers?
Trog: [Laughs] You—Yeah.
My new favorite game, peppers.
[Baaulp is still laughing, Wayne laughs again]
Gir: Hey, that’s my favorite friend!
Trog: Um, here’s something that you guys
have been playing that I have not been playing,
but I want to hear about it, and that is the
game called Fuser.
Which is like a little DJ game.
Baaulp: Oh, yes!
Trog: And that game looks like a lot of fun.
At the time of this recording, Scorpy, our
friend that you probably know if you’re
listening to this, did a stream of it last
night that I watched, and I was like, “Dang,
I gotta play this game.
This looks like so much fun.”
Gir: The short, sweet, and simple is: fun
game, cool mechanics, needs more songs.
Baaulp: Which it will have, it will get.
It will get.
Yeah.
Wayne: Needs more songs, but the songs are
like, extraordinarily expensive.
It’s like, if you want all the songs that
they release in a month, it’s seventy bucks
a month.
Trog: That is pretty—I mean, here’s
the thing, so it’s Harmonix, right?
It’s the people who made Rock Band and the
early Guitar Heroes, like that’s how their
DLC has always worked.
They do not put out—Like, they put out a
lot of DLC with the idea that you’re just
going to pick what you like, you’re not
going to get all of it.
Gir: Yeah.
Wayne: Yeah, like it makes sense-it makes
sense, like, three-it’s three dollars a
song, three songs a week, or something like
that.
Or maybe it’s two dollars a song, I’m
not even sure, but yeah, you definitely just
want to buy the ones you’re familiar with.
Baaulp: What my opinion on it is that this
might be my game of the year, this year.
Like it is a very fun game.
It’s weird because it’s far from perfect,
I think the campaign like, uh, okay so, for
reference, to unlock all of your DJ abilities,
right?
Like, that’s the only way I know how to—
[Gir laughs]
Baaulp: To unlock all the DJ abilities like,
uh, like noi—Filters, or like, y’know,
the ability to lower or raise the volume,
you have to play through the campaign, right?
Wayne: Campaign sucks.
Gir: It does.
Baaulp: The campaign sucks, and the main reason,
to me at least, aside from the cutscenes,
which you can skip, right?
You can skip the cutscenes, if you think the
cutscene’s annoying just skip them.
But the campaign is weird, because they try
to gamify DJ elements.
And this game isn’t like a rhythm game,
right?
You’re not hitting notes to a beat, you’re
not-you’re not, yeah, you’re not hitting
buttons to a beat or anything.
You’re-it’s like, okay, you’re a DJ,
just do these things, fulfill these requests,
do these things, and it’s like, it struggles
at that.
It struggles at turning it into a game, right?
Where like, you get scored one-to-five, right?
One-to-five stars.
And what ends up happening is by the end of
the campaign they’ve loaded on so many different
mechanics, ‘cause there are a lot of mechanics,
right?
They do a good job of like, giving you the
essence of feeling like you’re a DJ, right?
But, they are expecting you to go so ham on
these mechanics that…
Scorpy put it—Scorpy hit it right on the
head, it sounds like you’re making YTPs,
‘cause it’s like—
[Trog laughs]
Baaulp: —“Okay, play-play-play y’know,
okay, play these instruments,” So I’m
like going, I’m like tabbing over to this
like, part of my HUD, I’m like, playing
3 notes on like a synth violin, moving on
because I need to throw down some like Sean
Paul to fulfill this other request, and then
I’m like, constantly muting and unmuting
tracks, it’s like, this is no longer music,
but I’m doing it and it’s giving me four
stars.
[Laughs] So it’s like, y’know, it’s
weird.
Log: Yeah.
It’s annoy—It keeps-it keeps asking you
to do something that’s bad, like it-like
the stars can align and it can just tell you
like, “Alright, uh, mute half your tracks.
Alright, you done with that?
Mute your other tracks.
Leave like one drum track on, and let that
play for like, ten seconds.”
Wayne: Because the act of like, mixing a DJ
set is very subjective, like-like the score
system might as well just be fucking random,
and I hate it.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Wayne: It’s like, I’ve got something good,
it’s like, “Alright!
Now use three discs from Macklemore’s Thrift
Shop!”
And I’m in like a fucking like-like R&B
set and I’m like, it’s just like, awful.
Gir: In a country set.
Wayne: And then you get the fuckin’ clown
saxophone [Wayne imitates the horn segment
of the song], which like, you can make work,
Scorpy’s-Scorpy’s proven that.
But the—And then, yeah, like Log’s said,
you’ll just be in the middle of a track
and it’ll be like, “Alright, now fade
out all of your instruments!”
And it’s like, I don’t-I don’t want
to do that!
And then you get someone in the crowd that’s
like, “I gotta hear Nu ma Nu ma!”
[Trog laughs]
Wayne: And it’s just like everything I’m
playing sounds like shit, and the sad part—The
campaign is long and you have to play it to
unlock everything.
Gir: Yeah, it’s frustrating.
Wayne: And I like—It, for me, for some people
who really like the game like Scorpy, and
like you, Baaulp, you guys have been motivated
to play it enough to unlock most of the shit,
I’m like done.
I don’t think I’m gonna play Fuser anymore
because the campaign is that annoying for
me.
Baaulp: Wow.
Gir: It’s-it’s a slog.
Baaulp: You’re not gonna just tough it out?
Wayne: It’s a fucking slog, and frankly,
I don’t get enough out of the game to like,
keep going, like maybe I’ll keep doing it,
but I don’t know.
Trog: I mean, do you think eventually somebody
will just create like, “Hey, run this cheat
table, or download this save file, or—”
Wayne: I hope.
That’s what I hope, but like, the-the game
is very online integrated—
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: And I think they might like, god, imagine
getting banned for hacking in a fucking DJ
game.
[Trog laughs]
Log: Well it just depends, if there’s local
files for like the-the purchasable songs and
clearing the campaign and stuff like, I can
imagine there’s something like that.
Wayne: Something like that might happen, but
then it’ll-I bet it’ll block you from
playing online multiplayer, which is the best
part.
Baaulp: No, I don’t think they’d—Hopefully
they wouldn’t do that.
Well, here’s the thing, the campaign is
longer than it seems, but what I did was I
just sat down one night, and I was just like,
“Yeah, this campaign sucks, I’m just gonna
go through it.”
Wayne: Can you-can you fail?
Baaulp: It’s very hard to fail.
Wayne: Someone just make a fuckin’ bot that
plays the whole campaign for you.
Trog: Yeah, just a macro.
Wayne: Just like fuckin’, yeah.
Baaulp: What I did, and I assume Scorpy did
the same thing, is I just sat down one night
and I was like, “Yeah, this campaign a slog,
I’m just gonna go through it ‘cause I
like this game enough.”
And that’s the game’s major blemish.
It’s-it’s—It has two blemishes, but
one is like, it’s about the price.
So, the first blemish is—
Gir: There’s three blemishes, then.
Baaulp: Really.
Gir: Mhmm.
Baaulp: The first blemish is that the campaign,
it’s a slog, you need to go through it to
unlock everything, but what I did was I just
sat down, I was like, I just went through
it.
And it took me—Really, it only took me one
night, ‘cause you-like, I didn’t-you don’t
get much aside from XP which you use to unlock
more songs from—And you can get XP other
ways, like, so I was like, I’m just gonna
get three starts on every part, fuck it.
And I’m done.
I finished; I’m done.
Wayne: The campaign also has, like, there’s
cutscenes, they’re so bad.
Baaulp: Yeahhh.
Wayne: They’re just like, they created these
fake DJ personas that are the most obnoxious,
like, annoying characters with awful writing,
and then like, then the cherry on top is they
all look scary.
Their art-the art style for like the faces
in that game is this weird mix of like, Overwatch
and like, DreamWorks characters, and it’s
like, unsettling.
Baaulp: Uncanny valley.
Wayne: It is nearly uncanny valley—Yeah.
The best-looking character is the kid who
wore a mask the entire time ‘cause I couldn’t
see his face.
Baaulp: Yeah, I agree.
It’s kind of weird because it’s like,
they’re realistic, but just not realistic
enough where it’s like, “This is like
a marionette thing.”
Gir: It doesn’t help that they all have
mocap.
[Wayne laughs]
Baaulp: Yeah, like I wish-I wish they were
less detailed, ‘cause then that would look
fine, y’know.
The other thing is the price tag.
It’s sixty bucks, which is fine for like
a new big budget game, but when you add the
fact that you’re probably gonna get DLC,
like it adds up.
Some people might not be into that, that’s
why it’s like, that may or may not be a
concern for you.
What was the third thing you said?
You said—
Gir: The third thing for me is the multiplayer
is just incorrect.
Baaulp: Oh, yeah.
Gir: They set it up incorrectly.
Wayne: It needs to be more configurable.
Gir: It is called co-op freestyle, but there
can be an individual winner.
That-that co-op—There is neither co-op nor
freestyle in that.
Wayne: I mean, it’s not really a winner,
it’s just like-it’s just like, “Oh,
you got the most likes from your friends,”
It doesn’t—
Gir: No, but it’s a-it makes it feel pointless,
‘cause you sit there, you have like thirty
seconds to do anything, and then your turn’s
over and you have to go through a cycle.
Wayne: You need more time.
Like the—It’s co-op in the sense that
like, wherever your friend leaves off, that’s
where you pick up, and like, you have to take
that set and turn it into something, that’s
why it’s co-op.
Gir: That also feels competitive.
‘Cause you can just—
Wayne: It becomes slightly more competitive,
especially when it’s in a streamed environment,
because then everyone in your chat is like,
“Oh, you fuckin’ lost, you got no likes!
Blah!
Wah!”
And like, then it becomes a little bit different,
but like it’s not really a winner.
Baaulp: Yeah, what I was gonna say is like,
yeah, it like—That mode is fine the way
it is, it’s just like so fast.
Each person needs like, minimum six minutes.
Gir: Six minutes?!
That’s a little too much.
Baaulp: Yes, yes!
‘Cause it’s freestyle!
You’re supposed to just jam out!
Wayne: I could see a mode where I’d want
six minutes.
Like, it should be configurable.
Like, let me—
Gir: Configurable, yes.
Sure.
Wayne: Two minutes-two minutes would be good,
but you get like, forty-five seconds.
It’s like—
Gir: Thirty.
Wayne: Is it literally thirty seconds?
There’s no way.
Gir: No, it changes based on BPM.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Gir: But it’s like, thirty to sixty seconds.
Log: Yeah, that’s even worse, you have to
pick a-you have to go slow.
You have to go slow to get any time.
And then sometimes-sometimes it bugs out and
you’re not allowed to like mess with any
of your discs for the first ten seconds.
Baaulp: Well, I assume that’s a bug that
they’ll fix.
Wayne: The nature of the co-op freestyle mode
becoming slightly more competitive—The fun
part is just fucking over your friends by
like, “Alright, Gir’s up next, BPM 3,000.
Alright, uh, six Soulja Boy tracks, and All
Star.
Alright.
There you go.”
And like—
Log: Swap in the-the Happy lyrics.
[Trog and Wayne laugh]
Log: [Singing] “Might seem crazy what I’m
‘bout to say.”
Wayne: [Singing] “Might seem crazy what
I’m ‘bout to say.”
Log: It always ends on like a specific bit,
whenever you’re done with your part, it
always ends with like a specific bit it trails
off and then goes to the next guy.
If you end it with Happy, it’ll always just
be Pharrell Williams going, “Might seem
crazy what I’m ‘bout to say.”
[Baaulp laughs]
Wayne: Being bad at that game is also just
funny, because like-I’ll just like stumble
over the controls or not pick the right track
and then all of a sudden you just have like,
one vocal track so low and nothing else just—“Don’t
let the walls cave in on you!”
And just like, ten seconds of silence ‘cause
that vocal track is just like, fucked.
Gir: ‘Cause you can’t remember which ones
are playing at what time.
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: Well, despite what all of you have said
about the bad parts of this game, I am still
very interested in playing it.
Wayne: At its core it’s great!
Baaulp: If you are like, the reason why I
point all those out is because if you are
willing to pay for the game, if you’re willing
to deal with a monetization model like a DLC
model that is exactly the same as the other
Harmonix games like Rock Band, and just know
that like mechanics are locked behind a campaign,
this game is like, legitimately the most fun
I’ve had in a-with a—With a single-player
video game in a long time.
Like, there have been days where I like, where
I’ll be like, “Oh, I’ll play some Fuser!”
And then I’ll play, and then I’ll look
at the clock and it’s like, “Oh, it’s
like, 4AM now.”
[Laughs]
Trog: Yeah.
It seems like that kind of game where—‘Cause
you can just put it on a mode where you just
like keep going, right?
Like it’s just infinite—
Baaulp: Yes.
The freestyle mode is fun.
Wayne: Yeah, the freestyle mode-that—I wish—If
the freestyle mode just had everything unlocked,
like effect-wise, it would be fine.
Gir: Yeah, Every.
Single.
Thing.
Wayne: It’d be perfect.
The game would be great.
Gir: My personal recommendation for Fuser
is give it like a month or two, let them release
more songs, see if they’ll mix up the freestyle
or the co-op freestyle, see if they add anything
to it, and then get it.
Trog: Yeah, I mean the good thing is, similar
to all video games that are released nowadays
is that it can get patched, y’know?
Like they can-they can change things, they
can add things, so.
Wayne: I am very curious to see what modders
do to it—
Trog: Yeah, custom songs.
Wayne: —because it is apparently made in
a format where that’s possible, and I’m
curious if people figure out how to put stems
into it proper, that like actually sound correct.
Trog: Being able to add custom music and specifically
have it work in multiplayer would be the funniest
shit ever.
Wayne: Oh, it’d be great.
Trog: That would be a no brainer.
Gir: I’d like to see people just make-just
make different assorted tracks of like, videos.
It’s like, it’s like, uh, all the CDI
cutscenes as tracks.
Trog: Yeah, like that would be great, are
you kidding me.
That’d be so good.
Gir: I would love that.
Baaulp: I keep saying this, but, it’s kind
of accurate.
It’s like, it’s not the best video game—
Gir: But it’s a good one.
Baaulp: —but it is an amazing toy.
Like, it is the best thing to just sit down
on and be like, “I’m gonna fuckin’,
just, this is the funnest I’ve had in a
long time, just messing with tracks.”
Wayne: This is the funnest I’ve had!
Baaulp: Yeah [laughs].
Log: This is too funnest!
[Wayne laughs]
Baaulp: This is too funnest!
I’m gonna eat up—Oh, let’s play peppers!
[Everyone laughs]
Trog: I was asking Scorpy about this yesterday,
I was asking if they had MIDI support, because
like, the way that the game is setup sort
of looks like they were kind of emulating
like, the idea of a MIDI controller with certain
parts of the UI, but there’s no like, there’s
no support for an actual MIDI controller.
I would love if the game supported a MIDI
controller at some point.
‘Cause that would add like another layer
of fun if you could use an actual DJ turntable
like with a MIDI output.
Gir: I’d like to see them actually make,
or have somebody make for them, a uh, peripheral.
Trog: A peripheral, yeah.
I think they’re probably done with the whole
peripheral game.
It-it didn’t work out for them in the end.
Gir: Them personally, sure.
But I could-I would-I could definitely see
a third party wanting to do it for them.
Baaulp: The one thing I want, and they don’t
even have to add this, but it’d be insane
if they add this—It doesn’t even go as
far as what Trog wants, just let me get my
André 3000 on, I want to be able to play
tracks in reverse.
Trog: That would be interesting.
That’d be cool.
I could see them adding more effects and stuff,
yeah.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Trog: Like, they have a good core of a game,
they just need to flesh it out, it sounds
like.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Wayne: The one thing that might make me go
slog through the campaign again is the fucking,
like, some of those effects seem like so much
fun, like the looping, and the distortion.
Baaulp: What I’ll say is—
Wayne: The stutter.
Baaulp: Skip every cutscene, they tell you
what you need to—
Wayne: Yeah, I already do.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Wayne: Don’t worry.
Baaulp: Skip—Yeah, skip every cutscene,
and just like—
Wayne: I kind of—I think I’m gonna try—Like
I honestly might just go in and try to play
it, like, blindly, like just pressing keys
and not even paying attention.
Baaulp: Nah, don’t do that, ‘cause the
key to getting at least three stars—
Wayne: It’s just so…
It sounds so bad!
It just makes me mad!
Like when they force me to drop in random
tracks and fuckin’ mute shit—
Baaulp: I know, I know, I know.
Yeah, it’s weird.
And like, I don’t even fully blame them
for that, because it’s like, how do you
gamify being a DJ?
Like, you’re not—You’re expressing,
not playing it.
Gir: How do you gamify subjective taste?
Trog: DJ Hero.
Baaulp: Yeah, you’re expressing, not playing
an instrument.
Y’know, so it’s like.
Gir: Yeah.
Trog: I mean, they tried it.
They tried it with DJ Hero, and it was just
kind of like, y’know, it was just a normal,
notes coming at you, press them to make them
disappear rhythm game, but…
Wayne: One of the weirder features of the
game is like, they have like instruments where
you can just like play loops of like, drum
pad instruments and they kind of suck.
Gir: They do, they sound like shit.
Wayne: Like they kind of just don’t really
fit, ever.
You have like—One of the earliest instances
in the campaign where I just got like, mad
at what the game was asking me to do was I
was doing a rap set, and like, it was all
like classic rap, so I’m playin’ like
DMX, I’m playin’ like Nelly, and then
it’s like, “Alright!
Now drop in a fancy piano loop!”
And the fancy piano it’s like, just like
classical piano.
Gir: It’s like a MIDI piano.
Wayne: And it sounds—It’s a classical
MIDI piano, and like, you got X—you got,
“X GONNA GIVE IT TO YA, HE GON’—”
[Wayne imitates a soft piano tune], and it’s
just like, what is this?
Gir: And then you have an elf in the background
playing his piano, and it sounds like shit.
Wayne: What is—I don’t know, like why
did it—and that was the mission where it
introduced that to me, and it’s like, why
do you want me to do a rap set and then you
give me this shit, this trash?
Gir: Yeah, I don’t know.
Wayne: It’s inexplicable.
Gir: I would love for them to just not lock
that behind the campaign.
I’d like for them to patch that out, I don’t
know—I understand that they wanted to use
it as a tutorial, uh, I think I would rather
learn by just playing with the tools than
being forced to use them.
It’s more fun.
Wayne: What else we’ve been playing?
Gir: Oh?
What else we’ve been playing?
The answer to that is… uh…
Wayne: Welcome to WayneRadioTV’s Dead by
Daylight killer tutorial.
Gir: I have-I…
I—I’m struggling to think of what else
I’ve played.
Wayne: Lesson one, Barbecue and Chili.
Lesson two, Pudding.
Lesson three…
Log: Guilty Gear and Tekken.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Gir: Oh!
Teardown!
Wayne: Dead by Daylight is like all I’ve
been playing.
Gir: Teardown came down-came out and I had
fun with that for the first week.
Baaulp: Aside from Fuser, we’re all playing
very different things, actually.
This is the one week where, aside from Fuser,
a lot of us are just playing something different.
I’ve been playing Tekken, uh, I’ve been
playing a mishmash of things.
Gir: Instead of playing games, for the last
couple days I have restarted watching Star
Trek: Voyager.
Baaulp: Oh, shit.
Gir: And uh—
Baaulp: How’s that?
How’s the Neelix show?
Gir: Uh, there’s not one likable person
in that entire ship.
Trog: Bad.
Not even Neelix?
Gir: Everybody in that fucking ship sucks.
Wayne: Wait, is Voyager the one with Neelix?
Gir and Baaulp: Yes.
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: I thought that was Deep Space Nine,
I don’t know shit.
Gir: I’ve tried watching Voyager before,
and I-I got start to finish, but that was
like—I watched maybe four or five episodes
out of each season.
I’m trying to watch more this time around,
I’m almost on season four now, nobody—There’s
not a good person on the ship at all, for
real.
Baaulp: What?
You don’t like uh, Neelix?
Gir: No.
Baaulp: You don’t like Captain-Captain uh—
Trog: What about Tuvok?
Gir: Nobody likes Neelix, in fact, they go
out of their way to make fun of how awful
Neelix is at cooking, and yet he’s always
the cook.
Uh, the Captain is like, I don’t know, she’s
like, bipolar where one moment she’s against
something and immediately five seconds later
she’s all for it, uh—
Trog: I think Tuvok.
What about Tuvok?
What about, uh—
Baaulp: Yeah, what about Tuvok?
Gir: Tuvok is a Vulcan, and he’s a wet blanket
even for a Vulcan.
Trog: Sounds like the show sucks.
Gir: And yet it’s keeping my attention.
Log: Why don’t you just quit?
Baaulp: Why don’t you just watch TNG again?
Wayne: It’s true.
Gir: [Laughs] I can’t-I can’t, I’ve
done it like three times, I can’t.
Log: Why don’t you type any given word on
Netflix and watch it?
You could type in pepper.
Wayne: Netflix sucks.
Baaulp: What’s better?
Surviving R. Kelly or Voyager?
Gir: Voyager.
Wayne: Other than shows I’ve already seen,
there’s genuinely nothing on Netflix that
like, I’ve wanted to watch at the moment.
The uh—
Gir: Something that just came across my eyes
today on Netflix was something called uh,
what was it, it was like, “Son of Odin,”
or some shit?
What the fuck was it?
Trog: I don’t know, you tell me.
Gir: Okay, I will tell you, Trog.
It was called, “Son of—Blood of Zeus.”
Trog: Wow.
What’s it about.
Gir: And I—I don’t know.
Wayne: Why’d you even bring it up.
Gir: It just looks interesting.
Log: It’s about-it’s about Hades.
Gir: I was hoping somebody had actually played
it.
Or watched it, rather [laughs].
Wayne: You heard of—"Alright guys, I was
on Netflix today, I saw show called Haunting
of Bly Manor.
I don’t know anything else.
Conversation over.
Um… [laughs].”
Gir: I was hoping someone had seen it!
Log: I typed in Pepper and it gave me results
that were not related to pepper.
Wayne: I went on Netflix and I shaw [laughs]—I
saw a show called Peppers and I watched it.
Baaulp: And it was just a video of people
eating peppers.
Wayne: And then I got a big urge to play Peppers.
[Trog and Baaulp laugh]
Log: The first result is called Peppermint,
but it’s not out yet, but the rest of the
results are like Maria, PJ Masks, um—
Trog: Hmm.
Log: It’s like a fusion of kid’s shows
and also like,uh—
Gir: People with guns.
Log: Military action shows starring Matt Damon
and Ryan Reynolds [laughs].
Wayne: Have you guys ever watched a Hallmark
movie?
Baaulp: Yes.
Wayne: Their existence perplexes me.
Their—It-it-it is—
Gir: Well, you’re not a fifty-seven year
old woman!
Wayne: I know!
I’ve watched one because like, a while—a
long time ago I dated a girl who thought they
were like kind of entertaining and kind of
funny, and I watched one and it was just the
most like, drivel—
Baaulp: Milquetoast.
Wayne: —just like, milquetoast thing.
It was a Christmas movie about a knight who—
Baaulp: [Crosstalk] Wait, wait!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wayne: —went forward in time and falls in
love with a white girl.
Baaulp: [Crosstalk] Dammit.
Wayne: What?
Baaulp: Dammit.
I was-I was gonna guess the—I wanted to
guess.
I wanted to guess.
Gir: I wouldn’t have guessed a knight travelling
through time, to be fair.
Trog: No, that-that sounds interesting.
Wayne: I mean, the concept there was a little
bit wild, but it was just boring as fuck—
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: And it was just like—And the knight
was like—They didn’t even do anything
interesting with it, it was just like, the
knight would be on a horse and like, he’d
see a car and be like, “That’s a strange
horse.”
And he was way too calm, and it just sucked.
Trog: [Using a deep voice changer] “What
a strange beast.”
Gir: Did the lady say that he was her knight
in shining armor?
Wayne: Probably, I don’t remember.
[Gir laughs]
Wayne: There was some weird subplot about
the knight being cursed by like a witch, and
like the witch was also travelling through
time, and it-and then like-I don’t know…
Gir: Hallmark had to water it down for being
too exciting.
Wayne: The other Hallmark movie we watched
was like, it was-it was literally about ChristianMingle.com
like, the website.
Baaulp: What?
[Gir laughs]
Trog: Like sponsored?
Wayne: And it was like, it was about-it was
about a woman who wasn’t Christian like,
thinking that all the men on regular dating
sites were bad and not good, so she went on
ChristianMingle.com and started dating Christian
men and pretending to be Christian, and then
she goes to like-then she goes on like a…
like a—What do you call it when you go to
another country, you like, build houses?
Like a mission—
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: Like a mission trip or whatever they
call it.
She goes on like a mission trip to Mexico
and it got a little weird and like and then
they’re like-and then they figure out she’s
not Christian and they’re like, “You lied
about your faith.
I’m sorry but God says I can’t date you
anymore,” and then they break up.
Baaulp: Ha.
Wayne: But then she-but then she really starts
reading the Bible and she’s like, “Wow,
this God stuff’s pretty great,” and then-and
then they fall in love and go to church together.
The reason I bring this up—
Gir: Oh, that movie has a bad ending.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Wayne: I think—I saw this I think like-I
don’t remember where I saw it, but like
I saw this sweepstakes really recently where
the number one reward is that you get to star
in a Hallmark movie, and that is like the
craziest-that is like the craziest fucking
sweepstakes—
Trog: Oh god.
Baaulp: What?
What?
Gir: The lamest.
Wayne: No, ‘cause to me, like, what would
happen if you won and you like, sucked.
Trog: Were bad.
They could do a lot in editing.
[Wayne laughs]
Baaulp: Okay, okay, if you had to wager-if
I had to wager a guess, there’s no way in
hell they let you play the white couple that
actually falls in love.
When they say star, you’re probably like
a secondary-like a supporting character.
Wayne: God, that’d be so funny.
I like-I almost wish I could win.
Like, that would be fucking hilarious.
Like, I’m just streaming and it’s like,
“Hey guys, I’m in this Hallmark movie,
go check out the Christian Mingle official
movie!
Go watch that shit.”
Baaulp: I’m the guy in the background eating
corndogs while the white couple falls in love.
[Wayne and Gir laugh]
Wayne: It would be sick.
I would love to be in an awful movie.
Just a trash, like—
Trog: It would be fun.
Gir: That’s something, is I’ve always
kept my eye out for Neil Breen doing casting
calls here in Vegas.
Trog: Mhmm.
Baaulp: Oh yeah.
Wayne: That is like-that would be mmm, man.
I would fly out and like, also audition if
that happened.
Like, oh man that would be amazing.
Gir: Mhmm.
Trog: Audition?
[Baaulp laughs]
Gir: You know he does auditions, don’t even—
Trog: You just mean show up?
I don’t think that there’s going to be
auditions.
Wayne: I think he does auditions, but the
terms of which you actually get put in the
movie are actually incredibly subjective and
bizarre, like—
Gir: Here’s how I guarantee I could get
in, is he would show me whatever script I’m
doing, and I’d be like, “Oh, you wrote
this?
This is incredible!”
I would just have to appeal to his fuckin’
ego [laughs].
Wayne: You just kiss his ass, just-just kiss
his bony ass and you’ll get in the movie.
Gir: “Oh man, I hope your balls are out
in this movie!”
[Baaulp, Log, and Gir laugh]
Wayne: I feel like he could—[Laughs] “Are
we gonna see you balls, Neil?”
Oh, man.
Gir: “Mister Breen!”
Wayne: The uh—“Mister Breen!”
[Gir and Baaulp laugh]
Wayne: I feel like he would turn you away
on such like, bullshit terms like, “Oh,
you’re too young and I don’t like your
hair.”
Like I feel like he’d pick some like egotistical
bullshit reasons for kicking you out.
‘Cause you know how far up bone his ass—his
own ass he is.
Baaulp: “Y’know, I don’t like that you
just came in here with a habanero and just
ate it.”
Wayne: [Laughs] “Listen, we don’t play
peppers on set.”
Baaulp: [Crosstalk] “Yeah, we don’t play
Gir: “We don’t eat anything but tuna on
this set.”
Trog: “We only play peppers if you bring
enough to share with everybody.”
[Wayne laughs]
Gir: Dude, if you walked in with a crate of
peppers you would be guaranteed to be on that
movie, I-I’m certain.
Wayne: Yeah, just bring a bunch of food.
Just gotta find out what Neil Breen’s favorite
food is and bring it to the audition and you’ll
get in the movie.
Trog: Figure out what his favorite pepper
is.
Gir: You know what his favorite food is.
Wayne: What is it?
Gir: Tuna!
Trog: It is tuna.
It’s canned tuna.
Wayne: Oh yeah!
It is tuna!
Baaulp: Cans and cans of it.
Wayne: I forgot that that’s like, that he
writes himself to eat like, twenty cans of
tuna per movie.
Trog: Alternatively, that’s just the cheapest
prop food he could find.
[Wayne laughs]
Baaulp: That’s also true.
Yeah.
Gir: Tuna’s not cheap!
Tuna is not cheap.
Trog: Canned tuna is not expensive.
Log: He doesn’t eat it at all, he scoops
it out and leaves it on the ground.
Wayne: We know from doing low budget, public
access programming that tuna is the cheapest
prize you can get for your participants.
Baaulp: Oh my god.
Trog: That’s true.
[Gir and Wayne laugh]
Log: Neil Breen, I mean, he was-he was the
one that lost at the foot of the temple of
Olmec all that time ago.
Gir: Oh.
[Wayne laughs]
Log: He still-he’s still reaping the rewards.
Wayne: They got him addicted!
[Baaulp laughs]
Wayne: He got addicted to StarKist tuna!
Log: His fall from grace started way before
his brain reached the maturity level of thirty-five.
[Wayne laughs]
Gir: Damn, he really fell from grace.
Wayne: Don’t eat tuna before you’re thirty-five
or you get addicted!
Trog: We should-we should put an age limit
on tuna.
Gir: Yeah, he was only twelve when he was
on that show, now he looks like he’s sixty.
Wayne: Do you guys like tuna?
Trog: Sure.
[Unintelligible].
Baaulp: I like real tuna!
I like tuna that’s not in can, like, I—Like,
tuna’s one of the things I like to get when
I go to sushi places, like when it’s like-whether
it’s raw or actually cooked—
Gir: Oh, you got Baaulp going.
[Wayne laughs]
Baaulp: I like tuna.
But the stuff you get out of cans like, euuhhnn.
Log: It’s weird how the difference is.
‘Cause like, yeah, you see like a piece
of red tuna on some sushi rice and you’re
like, "Yeah, that’s three hundred dollars."
[Trog laughs]
Log: Uh, and then you get a can of it and
it tastes just kind of mediocre on a sandwich.
Wayne: Well, there’s many kinds of tuna!
Baaulp: Yeah, there’s multiple kinds of
tuna.
Wayne: Do you have any foods that when you
were a kid you ate so much that you can’t
fucking stand them now?
‘Cause like for me that’s—
Trog: Yeah.
Gir: Yes, called Cheetos.
Wayne: Tuna fish, like, tuna fish sandwiches,
when from like age of zero to like, six, were
all I ate, specifically like, tuna fish sandwiches—whenever
you’d take the canned tuna you’d mix it
in with a little bit of mayonnaise, and then
like you’d put that on a sandwich and what
my mom would do specifically, I’ll never
forget this, is like, most kids when they
have a sandwich, the mom, the dad will cut
off the crust or whatever.
For me, my mom would cut it up into little
like, cubes.
So, it was little bite sized finger food pieces
of sandwich and I loved that shit and it was
all I would eat!
And now like, the smell and the sight of like,
that kind of canned tuna fish makes me want
to fucking vomit and explode.
I hate it so much.
Gir: I-I am dead certain we’ve gone over
this.
Wayne: Maybe.
Trog: Tuna?
I don’t think so.
Gir: Not just that specifically, I mean in
general.
‘Cause I do remember—‘cause you also
said something about like uh, peanut butter.
You hated peanut butter.
And then you like it again.
Wayne: I mean, we also might have talked about
that off podcast.
Trog: We also might have talked about peppers
before.
Gir: I don’t know, we can’t keep track,
there’s been too many podcasts, there’s
been eighteen of these fuckin’ things!
Wayne: Y’know, y’know, y’know, there
is—there is a dedicated fan out there who
is transcribing all of the podcasts into text
form, I bet we could ask them.
I bet we could be like, “Can you like-can
you write down like a list?”
Baaulp: They’re a scribe?
Wayne: We do have a scribe!
I wish I knew their name!
Thank you to whoever-whoever this is!
I know that they post them to the WayneRadioTV
wiki.
The um—
Baaulp: We can­-we got—Well-well thank
you.
Well, thank you.
Wayne: Thank you.
The um, but—a compiled list of every topic
we’ve ever brought up would be like, amazing.
Gir: It’d be a long list.
Trog: And we—Yeah.
Wayne: It would be a long list, but—
Baaulp: You know what, uh, I am burned out
on when it comes to food?
This one’s surprising.
Chips.
I don’t like chips.
It isn’t as bad for you, I won’t like
retch when I see chips.
If someone offers me chips I’d have like,
one or two or three, but like, I don’t-I
won’t ever buy-I won’t buy chips for myself.
Chips are just something I don’t want anymore,
y’know what I mean?
Log: I don’t care about regular potato chips.
If it’s like a special-specially cooked
potato chips, like fresh out the oil, yeah.
Those are good.
Wayne: Yeah!
That’s what I was gonna say, have you-have
you ever had like, restaurant made like, fresh,
literally just cooked potato chips?
That shit’s amazing.
Baaulp: Yeah, and—yeah, yeah!
I’ll have like, a handful.
That’s it.
I’m not gonna like, go down on ‘em, right?
And the reason—
Wayne: What’s the best—
Trog: Baaulp will not go down on chips.
You heard it here first.
[Baaulp laughs]
Wayne: What is the best appetizer you’ve
ever had?
Trog: Mozzarella sticks.
Log: Best appetizer?
Wayne: Yes.
Log: Um—
Wayne: I have a very specific answer.
Log: There’s a place around here where one
of their appetizers is like, wonton nachos,
which sounds really stupid, but it’s actually
really good ‘cause it’s y’know, the
wonton stuff and chicken and like, basically
just like—it’s like nachos but with like,
Asian ingredients instead of, y’know, Tex-Mex
type stuff.
And it winds up being really—like the wonton
in place of the nacho chip is actually really
good.
Wayne: I went to this Italian restaurant like
a while back—
Baaulp: [Crosstalk] Hey Mambo, Mambo Italiano—
Wayne: —and they had an appetizer that was
called like—You said “Aye, mama,” coincidentally,
they were called mama’s chips.
They were called mama’s chips—
Gir: He said Mambo, but—
Wayne: What it-what it—Shut up.
What it was, was a plate of like super thinly
sliced eggplant—
Baaulp: Oohhhh.
Wayne: —that was then fried like they were
potato chips, so super thin, fried eggplant
chips with like, this delicious cucumber yogurt
dip that you would dip it into, oh my god—
Gir: Like tzatziki?
Wayne: Yes, the tzatziki—
Baaulp: Yo, that sounds good.
Wayne: It was so good, oh my god, I could
have ate the whole plate and been very sick.
Baaulp: You can probably replicate that at
home!
That might not be too hard!
Wayne: It was a very like, it was a very like
fine fry and cut job, it was professionally
made.
Baaulp: [Crosstalk] It was like-it was like-it
was like paper thin?
Wayne: Yes!
That’s why it was so good.
Like, for me, eggplant is—I don’t really
like eggplant.
Normally like a thick cut of eggplant I honestly
can’t stand it, but when it was this thin,
oh my god it was so good.
It removed all the texture bits I didn’t
like.
Gir: I can’t say my brain has ever logged
an appetizer on like a favorites list, I don’t
usually have many appetizers to begin with.
Wayne: Mozzarella sticks!
Perfect.
Ten out of ten.
Gir: So, I would say like mozzarella sticks
or uh, bloomin’ onion.
Wayne: [Laughs] I do love that you’re—
Gir: I don’t know.
Wayne: Like Log and I have a specific dish
from a specific restaurant, and it’s like,
“Best appetizer I’ve ever had?
Mozzarella sticks.
Does it every time.
Perfect.
Number one [laughs].”
Gir: I mean—
Trog: Literally, literally, I wish I had mozzarella
sticks right now.
I would—
Wayne: Me too!
[Unintelligible].
Trog: I would leave this podcast to go get
mozzarella sticks.
Baaulp: I might go get some mozzarella sticks
tomorrow, fuck!
Gir: I don’t usually do appetizers, I just
jump right into the main course and be done.
Wayne: I love a good appetizer!
Log: Enjoy the-enjoy the trip, MasterGir!
Wayne: Calamari?
Calamari?
Ooh!
Y’all like calamari?
Gir: I don’t eat much!
Log: You gotta eat some more!
Gir: Fuck cala—Oough, I hate squid!
Wayne: You hate calamari?
AAAH, fuck!
You crazy!
Trog: Eh, squid’s, y’know.
It’s good.
Log: Have-have some cheese fries.
Wayne: Yeah!
Poutine!
Log: Y’know, mozzarella sticks are good,
I think the favorite-I think my—Whenever
it’s not like a specialty, the thing that
I like the most, and it’s good because they’re
readily available in Texas, is fried pickles.
Trog: Those are pretty good, yeah.
Baaulp: Ohh, yeah, fried pickles are good!
Wayne: I will say, not my favorite, but I
do like ‘em.
A good plate I had at some restaurant was
like fried pickles and cheese curds, and it
was very good.
Gir: I’d try it.
I remember watching Billy and Mandy once and
one of the characters dicked-dipped a pickle
in uh, chocolate.
Wayne: They dicked.
Gir: They dicked a pickle.
Wayne: They did not—No one got dicked down
on Billy and Mandy.
Please don’t say that on our podcast.
Gir: [Laughs] Shut up!
Log: “Buenos dias.”
Gir: They di—[laughs].
Wayne: “Buenos dias, Mandy.”
Gir: They dipped a pickle in chocolate—
Wayne: [Crosstalk] “Imbecil!”
Gir: —and I was like, “Oh, that looks
gross, I’m gonna try that [laughs].”
Trog: And how was it?
Wayne: Salty sweet!
Gir: So I took a pickle and dipped it in some
like, I dipped it in some like, Nutella, and
I ate it and was like, “Oh my god, that’s
actually not bad [laughs]!”
Trog: I don’t know, I feel like a pickle
would be like, too sour for chocolate.
Gir: It was alright!
Wayne: Too sour, too juicy, maybe.
Log: Peanut butter pickles is like uh, is
like a known thing.
Trog: Really?
That’s wack.
Gir: It’s actually not bad.
Wayne: That’s a little bit more like—Like
with peanut butter, like peanut butter isn’t
just sweet, it’s more savory than sweet,
unless it’s like super sugary.
Gir: Depends on what it is.
If it’s Skippy then it’s more sweet than
anything.
Wayne: Yeah, god I love crappy peanut butter,
like Jiff is so good.
Crappy sugar, like crappy for you peanut butter.
Gir: Uh-huh.
Baaulp: Uh, we wanna…?
Wayne: Questions?
Trog: Yeah, we should probably start doing
questions.
Baaulp: Peppers?
Wayne: Peppers?
Yeah?
Baaulp: Yeah, peppers?
Gir: Peppers?
You want some peppers?
Baaulp: You want to play some peppers?
Wayne: Peasants?
Trog: First question here from PepperGamer
is just the word, “Peppers” with a question
mark.
What do you think?
Wayne: “Will you play peppers on stream?”
And the answer is yes, I’m totally—Listen,
once this podcast is live, I’m gonna do
a stream where we’re just gonna play peppers.
Baaulp: Can we actually do that?
[Unintelligible].
Wayne: Yes!
We could do it!
We could get a bunch of peppers and we’ll
come up with some rules.
Trog: We will not.
Log: Here’s your pepper, bro.
[Wayne laughs]
Log: And it’s uh, you ever have your friend
pass you the weird third-party pepper and
it’s covered in Cheeto dust?
Trog: [Laughs] Yeah, you get our extra pepper
that we don’t use unless we have guests
over.
Wayne: Your Mad Catz pepper.
Log: Yeah, Madz Cat-Mad Catz pepper with the
see-through skin.
Gir: Yeah.
Wayne: Eeuugh.
Baaulp: Oh, no.
Extra seeds?
Log: The seeds are bright orange.
Gir: They just hand you a handful of seeds.
Trog: Alright, this is all we have.
Wayne: Eating a handful of jalapeno seeds
would just be an awful experience, just a
nightmarish encounter in life with those seeds.
Gir: That’s how you’d kill a peasant,
for like, for real.
[Wayne laughs]
Baaulp: But hey, y’know, if you’re down
I’m down.
Let’s play peppers.
Wayne: Peppers.
Wayne: Alright, first question from Zekiran,
“If you were a lich, what object would you
store your spirit in to keep it safe?”
Now, this is both—This is a question of
both like an object of importance to you,
but also, what is the smartest pick?
Like, what is this called?
A phylactery or something like that?
Baaulp: Yeah, phylactery, yeah.
Wayne: Phylactery?
Yeah, like you want to pick one that the-that
the adventurer who’s questing to kill you
and take out your lichliness from this world,
you want to put it somewhere they’d never
expect, or somewhere they could never get
to, where do you put your soul?
Gir: Easy.
Log: Nintendo DS.
[Wayne and Baaulp laugh]
Gir: You kidding me?
Wayne: Which one?
Gir: What color?
Trog: Funny that you would choose that one,
because I was thinking of picking a Wii U
because nobody wants to touch it or look at
it, so, it’d be pretty safe.
[Baaulp laughs]
Gir: My answer is-should be the obvious one,
where it’s uh, fake dog turd.
Trog: Yeah?
So obvious.
Baaulp: Just some like Dollar Store prank
toy?
Gir: Yeah, no one would bat an eye, nobody
would touch it if it was inside, they’d
be like, “Ooh, that’s gross.
I’m not going near that.”
If it was outside they would even like, notice
it.
Baaulp: But like, you’d have to protect
it, so it’d be a dog turd in a box.
Like, it’s like, obvious.
Gir: They go, “Oh, I got pranked,” and
close the box again.
Wayne: I would put mine inside of Asimo the
robot.
[Baaulp laughs]
Trog: Uh-huh.
Wayne: I would-I would put my soul in there
and like, everyone loves Asimo, no one would
want to hurt him, and like, he’d be walking
around so he’s on the go, so you can never
find him in one consistent place.
Trog: Yeah.
Baaulp: One problem, I’ll enlist the help
of the mighty warrior, a warrior immune to
Asimo’s charms, one who thinks Asimo is
lazy-a lazy good for nothin’ oaf.
Wayne: Hmm, maybe I take it back.
I think Baaulp’s is [laughs]—
Baaulp: You know who?
You know who?
Trog: Baaulp’s just poked a giant hole in
your theory.
Gir: No, the flaw here—You’re not even
thinking.
The flaw here is Asimo would fall down a flight
of stairs and destroy himself [laughs]!
Wayne: Oh yeah!
What if he falls down the stairs and my soul
cracks and dies!
“So cry me a fucking river!
DIE!”
The fuckin’ [laughs]—
Log: Asimo is constantly in danger.
Gir: Yeah!
From himself!
Wayne: Okay, okay, because I just fucking
screamed that and no one’s gonna know what
it is, we got a Video of the Times for this
podcast is, uh, “Asimo Brutal Stair Fall,”
or whatever the fuck it was called.
It’s a really good video of Asimo—You’ll
see.
Trog: Doesn’t even know the title.
I think it is called—Let’s see [typing
sounds].
Wayne: That’s literally—It’s like, “Brutal
Stair Fall,” or something like that.
Baaulp: Yeah, and then Karl Pilkington would
come out and just rip its head off.
Wayne: Okay, I need a better one than Asimo.
Trog: Yeah, it’s literally just called,
“Asimo’s BRUTAL Stair Fall,” that’s
the Video of the Times.
Wayne: I got it—
Log: Anyways, a Nintendo DS is good because
it’s fun and compact and you can’t break
it even if you want to.
Trog: Mhmm.
Wayne: In the Elephant’s Foot.
Log: Oh, they have to make a sacrifice.
Gir: What?
Wayne: I would use my lich powers to put it
in there safely, ‘cause I’m a lich, I’d
be able to endure the radiation.
And I can put it in the Elephant’s Foot.
I literally would be unstoppable.
Gir: What is the Elephant’s Foot?
Baaulp: You don’t know?
Wayne: The Elephant’s Foot is the center
of Chernobyl.
Like it is-it is ground zero of the Chernobyl
nuclear disaster.
Gir: Oh, okay.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Wayne: Have you-do you—Have you ever seen
a picture of it?
Look it up, it’s crazy.
Gir: I have—No, I know, I just didn’t
know that is what it was called.
Log: It’s a-it’s a vile pile of sludge,
and they’ve only been able to take pictures
of it with like a little robotic camera, ‘cause
if somebody else got close to it—
Wayne: You’d be dead in a day.
Log: They’d become-they’d become part
of the foot.
Trog: Ough, scary.
Wayne: I guess that means someone could still
kill me, but you’d have to, you’d literally
have to sacrifice yourself.
Like—
Baaulp: It’d be another-it’d be another
lich.
Wayne: Yeah, it’s a never-ending curse,
I hex the phylactery so that if you break
it, you become a lich.
Trog: But then, that’s like a reward for
some people.
Gir: Can you force somebody to be a lich?
Trog: Probably.
Wayne: It’s not real, you can’t-you can’t
do that.
You can’t become a lich, either.
Gir: Wayne, you’re breaking the rules.
Wayne: This isn’t-this is all fantasy.
Log: If I were a lich, I’d simply be nice
and then nobody would try to destroy my phylactery.
[Baaulp laughs]
Wayne: That’s true.
Baaulp: That’s a good tactic.
Trog: That’s a good idea.
Baaulp: You did the opposite, you’d-you’d
be like, “You wanna play on my DS?
That’s me!”
Gir: Stored in the moon.
Trog: That’s cheating.
Wayne: But then Neil Armstrong will get you.
Trog: Yeah, I’m gonna store it in uh, Alpha
Centauri.
That’s my phylactery, is the entire uh,
star system.
Gir: You can’t store it in a star!
Wayne: Buzz Aldrin will come and fuck your
soul up, bro.
Gir: He’s never makin’ it back.
Wayne: [Laughs] No, he’s goin’ back, that’s
where he’s gonna die.
Gir: This time he goes back he’ll be in
a cup.
Baaulp: Damn, bro.
Wayne: That’s rude to Buzz Aldrin.
Gir: [Laughs] It’s true!
Trog: Can you make a public apology to Buzz
Aldrin on our podcast.
[Wayne laughs]
Baaulp: Yeah, make a public apology to Buzz
Aldrin right now.
Gir: Buzz Aldrin, I’m sorry that the next
time you get to the moon you will be nothing
but ashes.
Wayne: I mean if-if we’re doing that, now
I have to apologize to Queen Elizabeth for
threatening to make her smoke a ghost pepper
or whatever.
[Gir and Wayne laugh]
Wayne: I mean, Log, if you’re a nice lich,
the thing is you’re gonna get some meanies
coming after you, and you’re gonna have
like, some fuckin’, like, “Oh, I hate
that guy, I hate that lich, he’s too nice
to people.”
Trog: He’s gonna have fun adventures, he’s
gonna be like a children’s cartoon character.
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: Fun Lich.
Wayne: Log the friendly lich.
Baaulp: If Wayne’s answer is the Elephant’s
Foot, my answer is Wayne.
Wayne will be my phylactery.
So it’ll be another lich!
Wayne: Yo, a chain of liches!
Baaulp: Yeah [laughs!]
Trog: Pretty smart.
Wayne: That’s kind of cool.
Baaulp: But it’s like a cascading effect
where if someone makes it to the Elephant’s
Foot and takes you down, it’s like a chain
reaction.
Wayne: Yeah.
Gir: Store your souls in each other.
Wayne: The source of all liches.
The issue there, though, is that if someone
like, tries to fight me and attack me, and
they deal a decisive blow, I won’t die,
but you will.
Baaulp: No, because you’re not dead!
You’re a lich!
Wayne: Well, but no, your phylactery—I-this
is hurting my head, this isn’t real.
Liches aren’t real, hopefully.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Wayne: Let’s move on [laughs].
Baaulp: Good thing liches aren’t real, that’s
our answer.
This is a good one.
I don’t have an answer for this, but you
guys might.
“What nightmare creatures haunted your mind
as a young child?
For example—”
Gir: Who asked that?
Baaulp: Uh… someone named Grungle.
Gir: Mhmm.
Baaulp: Now I have to do-do it all over again
from the top, thank you, MasterGir.
Gir: Yeah, you’re welcome.
Wayne: Do it.
Trog: Well, you didn’t say his name, you
do have to do it all over again.
Gir: Yeah!
Baaulp: I didn’t finish reading it!
Oh my god.
[Wayne and Gir laugh]
Gir: He’s supposed to say who’s so-and-so
last!
Trog: You’re supposed to say the name first!
Wayne: From the top!
From the top.
Baaulp: No, I don’t have to do that, I’m
reading the email as is!
Wayne: FROM THE TOP!
[Trog and Gir laugh]
Baaulp: Oh my god.
“What nightmare creatures haunted your mind
as a young child?
For example, the two creatures I was really
afraid of as a kid were the zombie cat from
a Goosebumps direct-to-video movie, and a
dead baboon.”
Woah.
Trog: Wow.
Wayne: Woah.
Baaulp: “I thought they both lived in the
dark hallway outside my room [laughs].”
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: Wow.
Wayne: A fucking undead baboon!
That’s awesome.
Baaulp: “Were you haunted by any imaginary
terrors?
Or were you fearless?
Sincerely, Grungle.”
Wayne: Uh, I have a few answers.
So, Baaulp, you don’t have an answer at
the moment?
Baaulp: I-I might not have a good answer,
‘cause, okay, what spooked me as a kid—I-I’ve
said this before, but I watched a lot of History
Channel as a kid, I thought Hitler would come
to get me.
Gir: That’s awesome.
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: That is not a fictional person.
Baaulp: That one was weird because I also-I-I
knew how irrational that was because all those
Hitler documentaries talked about how Hitler
ended his own life-took his own life in the
bunkers, so I knew Hitler wasn’t around
anymore, but it was just like—
Gir: He became a lich.
Baaulp: [Laughs] Oh no.
Wayne: I had that fear, too, after I watched
Dragon Ball Z: Fusion Reborn.
I was scared that Hitler would escape Other
World, but I knew Goten would protect me.
Trog: I thought you were gonna say, “I thought
Jenemba was gonna come and get me.”
[Everyone laughs]
Wayne: That too.
I was so scared of Jenemba.
Baaulp: The other thing that legitimately
kind of spooked me but like, I also knew they
weren’t real, was aliens.
I thought aliens were-I thought aliens were
scary, ‘cause they’re y’know, literally
otherworldly, but I also knew they wouldn’t
like, do anything.
I thought-like, I was a very grounded kid,
I knew like, “Okay, this is scary, but I
also don’t-can’t be real.”
Wayne: I know someone that is genuinely afraid
of aliens and it’s so funny to me.
Baaulp: Really?
Wayne: Like, it-it just cracks me the fuck
up, but uh, my uh, so my nightmare demons
when I was a child, I—The first one I’ve
told stories about on stream many times, but
there was a cow uh, we had a vacuum cover
for our vacuum cleaner that resided in the
living room that was like a cow woman, uh,
it was like-it was like a cow in like a old
timey, colonial maid outfit, and it was pretty
big, and it would rest on top of a vacuum
cleaner ‘cause it was supposed to cover
it and like hide it from the room.
So it was like, six to seven feet tall, and
it towered over me as like a young four year
old—
[Trog laughs]
Wayne: —and its soulless black eyes fucking
terrified me.
Its size, its look, everything about it terrified
me to the point that I would consistently,
constantly have nightmares that it would kill
my mom and take over.
Baaulp: Ough.
Wayne: And just like, like over and over I
never stopped having those nightmares until
they got rid of it.
And then, the first time they got rid of it,
I found it in their closet, and I was like,
“Fuck you!
You said you got rid of it!
You said you killed it!”
I was so—I felt so betrayed.
Um, second, I remember that the very first
time—Like, the very first night that I slept
in my new house the first time that I moved
when I was a kid, I had this nightmare of
these like, two Muppets with like, noodle
arms, that were just standing over my bed
waiting for me to wake up, to prove that I
was alive so that they could kill me.
Baaulp: Oh shit, that’s brutal, that’s
like—Holy shit!
Wayne: They had like, giant mouths and super
long arms and they just kept talking to each
other like, “If he opens his eyes, we’re
gonna eat him!
We’re gonna—” And then I remember the
nightmare ended with like-the nightmare ended
with like I moved a little bit and they were
like, “He’s awake!”
And they grabbed me and started swinging me
around the room in a 360 like a giant swing,
like King from Tekken.
Trog: Somebody is going to draw this now.
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: You’ve willed this into existence.
Gir: He had a Don’t Hug Me I’m Scared
dream.
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: They kind of were like Don’t Hug
Me I’m Scared characters, they were like
weird, eyeless Muppets with like, big, Pacman
mouths, yeah, and then—That one wasn’t
reoccurring, but that is the most vivid childhood
nightmare I ever had.
Baaulp: Yeah, that sounds very distinct.
That sounds like it’d scare the shit out
of me as a kid.
Wayne: The scariest part to me was-was like,
the very clear concept that these two, this
mother and baby Muppet puppet were like, “I
can’t wait till he wakes up so we can kill
him!
But if he never opens his eyes, he’s probably
dead.”
Or like, whatever the fuck they were saying.
Trog: Why-why did you have to be…
I mean, I guess you have to be alive for them
to kill you, but it’s like, the fact that
they would wait for you to show that you were
alive before attacking you is—
Wayne: [Laughs] I don’t know!
They wanted to see my fear.
I don’t know.
Trog: I guess so.
Gir: They didn’t want to waste their time.
Trog: Talking about aliens, ironically enough,
my childhood nightmare reoccurring nightmare
demon, and this is not a joke, even though
it’s going to sound like it, it was the
blue aliens from the Eiffel 65 Blue music
video.
Gir: No.
Wayne: OH MY GOD!
Baaulp Oh.
My.
God.
Wayne: Zorotl?
Trog: So that-that song came out probably
like, what?
I probably was like six or seven years old—
Baaupl: Oh.
My god.
Trog: —so first or second grade, just freaked
the shit out of me, I saw it on TV on like
the Disney Channel once and I like, couldn’t
sleep for months.
Gir: That’s insane.
Baaulp: We-we love Zorotl, how come you’ve
never talked about this?
Trog: Oh yeah, no, now-now I look and it’s
like I fucking love this shit, it’s so funny
because yeah, as a child, absolutely hated
it, made me hate the band Eiffel 65, nowadays
I’m totally into the shitty 90’s CGI aesthetic,
so, I’ve done a full 180 on that opinion.
Baaulp: You got over it.
Yeah.
Trog: But, at the time, fuck Zorotl, fuck
blue—Those things scared the shit out of
me as a child.
Baaulp: That’s so funny.
That’s so funny.
Gir: I’ve already talked about—and I’m
pretty sure it was on the podcast—how I
had like a Woody toy that scared me so bad
I buried him in my backyard.
What I haven’t talked about was another
toy that was given to me that scared the shit
out of me, which was like, some like walking,
talking pig toy?
And I don’t know what it was about this
thing, but—
Baaulp: Walking, talking pig toy?
Gir: It-you know like when a toy walks it
does like, kind of like a waddle—
Baaulp: Oh, yeah.
Gir: And it like, it had like little voice
lines, but something about that pig, I-this
was when I was like maybe five, so it was
a long time ago, something about that pig
scared me so.
Fucking.
Bad.
That I chucked that motherfucker into my closet
and buried him under so much shit and made
sure that closet door never opened again.
Trog: I’m surprised that you didn’t just
bury them outside, too, y’know like?
Just start like a little collection out there
of nightmares.
Gir: That was my first burying, it was just
underneath of items instead of dirt.
Trog: My first burying.
Gir: My first burial.
Log: Yeah, for me it was uh, the Sleestak
from Land of the Lost.
Gir: What?
Trog: I don’t know what that is.
Log: The Sle—
Gir: What?
Trog: Describe it.
Log: The Sleestak from Land of the Lost, it’s
like a lizardman.
And it’s like a-it’s like a lizardman
from a sixties show, so y’know.
Trog: Mhmm.
Log: I wasn’t afraid of them whenever I
was awake, but I would always have nightmares
about the Sleestaks that lived in the first
floor of my house, and if I went down to the
first floor, the chase was on.
And I’d have to run from the Sleestaks.
Trog: I typed in “Sleestak,” into Google
Images and I like that the first-or I typed
it into Google, and I like that the first
like, autocomplete was, “Sleestak images.”
People are just wild to see pictures of this
guy.
Wayne: I have one more, it wasn’t mine,
but it-it is one that my friend told me about,
like of something he experienced, that has
always stuck me as one of the funniest childhood
nightmares.
He-to him, the scariest nightmare he ever
had was like, he must have been like five,
he had a nightmare that he was in an empty
white void and eventually, after a certain
amount of time, a purple machine appeared
in front of him, and on top of it was Fred
or another character from Scooby-Doo, uh,
with a broom, sweeping the machine.
And it was-to him, he described it as like,
the deepest fear he’s ever felt.
And like, that is so funny to me, just indescribable,
incomprehensible fear.
[Trog laughs]
Gir: That’s just insane.
Trog: Brain chemicals are weird.
It’s so dumb, like, I-I have dreams, I can’t
remember the last time I had like, a true
nightmare, but I have like stress dreams and
anxiety dreams, and brains are so dumb because
even if I am having a stress dream that I’m
like, “This is a dream,” it still, like
the chemicals in your brain don’t go away,
it doesn’t matter if you realize that it’s
a dream, you still are going to freak out.
Gir: I mostly just get annoyance.
Like the worst the dream will get will be,
I’ll be annoyed.
I don’t really get even stressed anymore.
Wayne: For me, if like the stress trickles
into a dream, it doesn’t matter what the
fuck was happening in the dream, like just
something that I deem stressful that I don’t
want to happen in my real life will just happen.
Like I’ll be like, venturing through a castle,
and then like, I’ll start to feel that little
bit of stress, and all of a sudden Jazz will
fly out of my shirt and out a window and I’ll
be like, “No!
He’s gone!”
Trog: Yeah [laughs].
Wayne: And then I gotta stop questing and
go get my fucking pet bird.
Trog: Yeah.
Okay—
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: This is not related directly to the
question, but, I-I have a quick question about
dreams just because I was thinking about it
earlier today.
Have you guys ever gotten hurt in a dream?
Like-like have you felt physical pain while
dreaming?
Baaulp: What do you mean?
Wayne: Uh, like Frankie Muniz getting shot
by the bullets and feeling the burn?
[Baaulp laughs]
Gir: Uhm, kind of.
Trog: I, every once in a while, will actually
experience pain in a dream, and it’s really-and
it freaks me out.
Baaulp: That sounds so—What?
Trog: Yeah, and it’s like, I mean it-it
makes sense, right?
Pain is just a thing that your brain does—
Gir: A brain reaction, yeah.
Trog: So it’s like, earlier today, literally
earlier today, I was taking a nap, I don’t
even remember what the dream was about, I
was in some kind of forest, I reached down
into a plant, and my brain told me that that
plant was like, poisonous acid, and it made-it
like hurt my hand so bad that I woke up.
Baaulp: Woah!
Wayne: That’s crazy!
Gir: Oh, wow.
Baaulp: What?
Gir: That-that’s pretty intense.
Wayne: For-for me, almost any time like pain
would happen I get jolted out of it.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Wayne: Like-like for me, if a dream gets too
stressful, my go-to is to kill myself instantly.
[Gir, Trog, and Log laugh]
Baaulp and Gir: Holy shit.
Wayne: I have a very clear memory of like,
uh, having a dream when I was a little kid
where I was at like, Sea World, watching like
Shamu or whatever the fuck, and like a big
stadium with a pool in the center, and I remember
something started freaking me out so bad I
was like, and mind you, I was in like the
middle of the bleachers like-like hundreds
of feet away from the pool in the center,
I remember standing up and vertically leaping
into the center of the stage and into the
water and dying and waking up.
I remember that like [laughs]—
[Trog laughs]
Gir: That’s incredible.
Wayne, laughing: And I was like-and I was
like seven!
Trog: Death on contact with the water.
Log: You do it so cinematic, like, I could
just-if I know I’m in a dream I can just
force myself awake.
Trog: I can’t do that.
I don’t know why.
Wayne: Nowadays I can, but…
Baaulp: Yeah, that’s the-the thing with
Trog said, that is absolutely crazy to me,
because I’ve never felt pain in a dream.
I’ve never felt pain in a dream, because—
Wayne: Not that I can remember.
Baaulp: Yeah, one of two things-one of two
things will happen, either like—I am astronomically
clumsier in my dreams than I am waking up,
like, for some reason in my dreams—‘Cause
it’s weird, I’m not as clumsy in real
life, but in my dreams I always drop things
and like, I always trip, and those usually
will jolt me awake, right?
Log: Yeah, that’s normal.
Baaulp: That’ll usually jolt me awake, and
the same thing like, if I would ever be hurt,
I would usually just get jolted awake, and
I wouldn’t feel the pain, like that’s
crazy that you woke up and your hand hurt,
like, that’s crazy.
Trog: Yeah, I mean it’s the kind of thing,
right?
That it’s like, it just hurts while it hurts
and then it goes away ‘cause I don’t actually
have an injury, so it’s not like—
Gir: Yeah.
Trog: But it’s just like, yeah, I just-I
vividly recall earlier today taking a nap,
sticking my hand into a plant, and having
it physically hurt me.
Baaulp: And I-I’ve had dreams where I’ve
been injured before, but like—And I will
panic, like, y’know, I don’t know, I can’t
remember the last time I was like hurt in
a dream but like, I don’t know, maybe I
broke my arm or something in a dream, and
like, I’ll freak out, but when I wake up
I’m like, “Oh, I had a dream about breaking
my arm, good thing I didn’t actually feel-I
didn’t feel any pain!”
Like y’know.
Gir: The two things that come to mind is usually
if I have like a headache while I’m asleep,
I can feel the headache in the dream—
Baaulp: Oh well, yeah, that’s ‘cause that’s-you
have a headache, yeah.
Gir: Which is, that’s like the easiest example,
yeah.
Trog: That makes sense.
Gir: But I do remember, this was years and
years and years ago, having a dream where
some kind of snake bit me, and whatever it
did, whatever the venom did, it kept me from
being able to breathe properly and I couldn’t
speak, so I couldn’t tell anybody that I
got bit by a snake, so I couldn’t get any
help.
Trog: That’s a terrible nightmare.
Gir: And that was probably the worst-that
was probably the worst nightmare I’d—That’s
probably the last nightmare I really had,
actually.
And that was probably ten, eleven, twelve
years ago.
Trog: It’s funny that you mention getting
bit by a snake because a reoccurring theme
in my-in my anxiety stress dreams is there’s
always an animal trying to bite me, and I
have to like, hold its mouth open with my
bare hands.
[Gir and Wayne laugh]
Trog: This is a reoccurring theme in my dreams,
I don’t know why.
Gir: You ever been bitten by an animal?
Trog: No!
I’ve never gotten like, seriously injured
by an animal ever in my life, I love animals.
[Gir laughs]
Baaulp: You’re like fuckin’ Tarzan in
your dreams!
All the time!
Trog: Yeah, but it’s not like I’m cool
like Tarzan, it’s like, “Fuck, I have
to stop this giant snake from biting me on
my arm by like, holding its jaws open with
my fists.”
Baaulp: “I gotta pick these acid plants!”
Gir: But one more aside on the topic of dreams,
is uh, and I finally got a real confirmation
of this the other night, was y’know how
people say, “Oh, you can’t read in dreams,”
and people will be like, “Oh, bullshit,
yeah you can!”
I can confirm I read a street sign in my dream
like two days ago.
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: Yeah, sometimes I can read, like, I
almost feel like you can read in a dream if
the dream like, intends for you to derive
something from that reading.
Gir: Yeah.
Wayne: Like-like I’ve had dreams where I
get like a letter and I have to read the letter
like, to understand—Well, understand, quote
unquote, the dream plot, but like, I think
if I realized I was in a dream and I tried
to just read anything, that’s where like
the simulation falls apart.
Trog: I think the thing with reading in dreams
is that, it’s not that it’s impossible
to read in dreams, it’s just that sometimes
it is impossible to read in dreams, and that’s
why it’s used as like, a lucid dream trigger,
is that if you can-if you can tell that you
can’t read then it helps.
But also, I think it’s the fact that recognizing
that sometimes you can read in dreams, but
what you’re reading doesn’t make any sense
at all, whenever you think about it.
I think that’s also part of it.
Wayne: For me I can never-I can never like
intentionally trip of force a lucid dream
out of a regular dream, for me it’s always
like, I always like fall asleep weird and
like, enter a lucid dream immediately.
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: Like-like I know that I’m doing it,
like it’s not intentional, either, it just
happens.
Trog: Mhmm.
Wayne: Next question comes from Turkey Samich,
and they say, “If you could have any car
(including movie cars, rare one-of-one cars,
etc.) what would you pick?”
Lightning McQueen, I’d dissect him for billions
of dollars.
Trog: What do you think’s inside of Lightning
McQueen?
Like is it just a normal car in there?
Wayne: That’s what I’m saying, I would-you
would be rich.
Gir: Blood, guts, and poop.
Wayne: I-I think you would be rich if you
could get Lightning McQueen and figure out
what the fuck’s going on there and uh, I
mean you wouldn’t have to care ‘cause
he’s not human, either, he has no soul,
he’s a car.
Trog: Oh, okay.
Gir: He has no rights.
Baaulp: Ehh.
Wayne, laughing: He has no rights!
Trog: So, Wayne doesn’t care about the sentience
of a creature, simply that they have a human
soul.
Wayne: [Laughs] Listen, I’m just trying
to pick the optimi-the optimized answer.
Trog: Uh-huh.
Wayne: I don’t [laughs]—
Trog: You’re trying to get the high score
on this podcast question.
Wayne: Yeah.
Gir: Just want to find out why he sounds like
Owen Wilson.
Wayne: No, other than that joke, I don’t
even know if we should-like, do you guys have
an answer to the car question?
Baaulp: Uh, Mater.
So I can dissect him.
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: No, you can’t do that.
Wayne: Mater.
Trog: It depends.
Can I like, pick a car with like, special
properties or does it—
Log: Let’s just dissect every Disney car.
Wayne: Do you guys know any Cars characters
other than Lightning McQueen and Mater?
‘Cause I don’t.
Trog: Um, no, not really.
Baaulp: That blue Maserati that Lightning
McQueen wants to fuck.
Wayne: What’s her name?
Baaulp: I don’t know.
Trog: Yeah, exactly.
Log: There’s like a little fucker named
Luigi.
Trog: I feel like I remember—There’s a
big truck, right?
Wayne: Bro, that’s Mario.
Trog: There’s like a—
Wayne: You’re thinking of Super Mario Bros,
I know that Lightning McQueen is red—
Log: He’s like the-he’s like the little
forklift.
Wayne: It’s different.
Trog: Yeah, I remember that.
Wayne: What’s the little red car?
That goes kachow?
Oh yeah, Elmo.
Gir: From Super Mario Brothers?
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: I’d pick a clown car that I can fit
a hundred people in, but it’s really tiny.
Wayne: Funniest thing in the world, in the
history of me knowing my friends and us being
a group, is Baaulp accidentally calling Elmo
‘Mario’ in full honesty.
[Everyone laughs]
Baaulp: Listen, it’s red!
Trog: It’s red.
Baaulp: Yeah, it’s red.
I’m like a bull.
Trog: You’re right, Mario is red.
And Elmo’s Italian.
Gir: Yeah, he’s red, just like Goofy from
McDonalds.
Wayne: It’s like little Mega64 ArmorGames
video, “Is the red one Mario?”
Gir: I have no answer to the car question.
Wayne: Yeah, other than that stupid joke I
made I don’t have one, either.
Trog: I told you, I want a clown car that
works like clown cars do in cartoons.
Gir: I want the flying car from GTA Online.
Wayne: I wan the car from the Flintstones!
Trog: That one would suck, you’d have to
wheel it yourself!
Gir: Yeah.
Wayne: Yeah, but it’d be funny.
Trog: I mean, yes.
Also, I don’t think that car can turn.
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: Whenever you think about the logistics
of how that car is manufactured.
Gir: Y’know what?
For a real car, I-I actually would like a
DeLorean.
Like a real DeLorean, not the fucking Back
to the Future one.
Trog: Yeah.
That’d be cool.
I mean, they’re nice cars.
I don’t know, the thing is is that I’m
like, I’m not like a car person, and even
less than that I barely drive, so like, I
don’t know—
Wayne: I only brought the question up because
that answer popped into my head like instantly,
it was just dissect Lightning McQueen.
Baaulp: And you had to get it out.
Wayne: Yes.
Baaulp: Poltermice asks, “If you had the
option to create a convention for a game/concept,
without having to worry about money, time,
or manpower, what would you center it around
and where would—and what would be there?”
So basically, if you could will just magically,
any kind of convention for anything, what
would you do?
Trog: Hmm.
Baaulp: And that comes from Poltermice, thank
you very much.
Gir: I think the conventions for the things
I’m interested al-already exist.
Baaulp: Well, no, you’re thinking-you’re
thinking too low-level, I would have—
Wayne: PeppersCon!
Baaulp: Yes, like-yeah, like we could have
Pepperscon [laughs]!
Wayne: BalloonBlastCon!
Baaulp: Yeah, like we could have BalloonBoyCon,
like!
Gir: Balloon Boy Con [laughs]?
Baaulp: Yeah, exactly [laughs]!
Trog: I want a convention that is a convention
for people who are very rich and very generous,
and I will walk around and ask for money.
Gir: I was just about to say—The Give MasterGir
Money Convention.
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: Yeah.
[Baaulp laughs]
Trog: It’s for philanthropists, but it’s
for philanthropists who just like handing
me hundred-dollar bills.
Baaulp: For just you!
Gir: Nah, I’m gonna say I want the Bird
Box Convention.
Baaulp What is that?
Trog: Bird Box?
Gir: I want a convention of people that are
walking around with blindfolds on.
Baaulp: Ohhh, like that.
[Trog laughs]
Baaulp: Like Comic-Con but everyone’s blindfolded!
Gir, laughing: Yeah, everyone’s blindfolded!
Wayne: You’re gonna get ten concussions
on day one and uh, then you’ll be banned
from the venue.
Gir: No, they have to sign a waver before
entering that says that I’m allowed to let
them do that and laugh at it.
Wayne: No one will come.
Gir: No, it’s my convention and I say everybody
comes!
Wayne: [Laughs] In your fantasy world.
Gir: In my fantasy world everyone comes!
Wayne: Well, unlike you, everyone would come
to PeppersCon even if it wasn’t a fantasy
world, so, I’m like—
Gir: What if you’re allergic to peppers?
Wayne: I mean, they don’t have to come.
Baaulp: Syn-syn-synthetic peppers.
Wayne: Most people would go.
Baaulp: Syn-synthetic peppers [laughs].
Gir: Check out our new syn-peppers!
Wayne: We got hypoallergenic peppers!
Trog: I want a convention that’s like-I
want a convention that’s like uh, well what’s
the one, it’s CES, right?
That’s like the big tech—
Baaulp: Yeah, that’s more geared towards
general electronics, yeah.
Trog: Yeah, I want a convention that’s like
CES but the shit actually looks like it’s
from the future and it’s not just your juicer
connects to your Wi-Fi.
Wayne: Bullshit.
Gir: I was going to make a crude like, “Oh
haha sex toy convention,” joke, and I remembered
that’s just a thing.
Trog: I mean, yeah, that’s—
Wayne: Yeah, they do that.
Gir: That’s like several things.
Baaulp: They have those—
Trog: Imagine a CES where you go and all the
shit there actually looks useful and cool.
Baaulp: It’s like actual things from the
future!
Yeah, that’d be dope.
Real answer?
Like-like, okay, serious answer, a fighting
game like—So Magic the Gathering, I-I think
this ran for a while, I’m not sure, I haven’t
paid attention to like the competitive Magic
the Gathering scene, but since the Magic the
Gathering player base tends to be like older
people, it doesn’t-it’s not like typical
gamer things.
One of the coolest things that they would
have is the Magic the Gathering cruise, and
what it would be is, yeah, you just go on
a three-day cruise and everyone there plays
the same game.
Like everyone there plays Magic the Gathering.
And the other thing that was cool was like,
that was their convention and also like, people
would like-have like—There’d be like serious
panels on like, “Yeah, here’s how to get
really good at this game, like here’s what
you do, here’s how you like do this and
do that,” like I want that but for fighting
games.
Like, it’s not a tournament, it’s like
here’s an event where you show up if you’re
a fan of fighting games and you just play
all week and there’s just like serious discussion
about like, the state of things and like,
how to get better, ‘cause I feel like right
now every like, “Oh, how to get good at
this fighting game,” is like to me it seems
very gimmicky, and it’s like, there’s
no one who’s like-there’s no one who is
just like old and like, “Yeah, I’ll-I’ll
teach you how to play without-and I’m not
sponsored by like, anything, I’m just-I’m
just here to teach you for real, like in a
super accurate and detailed way, this.”
‘Cause like, I’m a little older, I’m-I’m
like closer to thirty now, I care more about
those things than I used to when I was like,
younger.
I think it’d be interesting.
Gir: Hey, Baaulp?
Two things.
One, I am very surprised your convention had
nothing to do with food.
Baaulp: What?
Trog: Yeah.
A little bit.
Gir: And two—
Wayne: DinnerCon!
Gir: Two, my real, real, final answer, uh,
I have to take a personality test and list
my favorite things in the world that I like,
and then everybody that wants to come to my
convention has to match that personality test.
Wayne: Self-centered?
Much?
Trog: So peppers and burying toys.
Wayne: Peppers and Dragon Ball Z and—
Gir: It’s the Stuff I Like Con.
Wayne: Robots.
Log: And not being wet in a car.
[Baaulp laughs]
Gir: That’s true, I don’t like being wet
in a car.
Log: What kind of personality test do you
take that tells you what you like?
That seems very specific.
Wayne: Yeah, I don’t know what the fuck
you’re talking about [laughs].
Trog: Yeah, that’s like—
Gir: No, I’m not-I say you do the personality
test and at the end you list the things that
you like on top of it.
Wayne: Yo Baaulp, if DinnerCon has any peppers
I’m fucking suing you.
[Baaulp laughs]
Log: Anyways, I want a french fry convention.
Baaulp: Oohhhh.
Wayne: Yeah!
Gir: I guarantee that’s real.
Log: The kind of stuff that I like and am
like, invested in, having a con-like I-I don’t
think I would want a convention just about
that, I feel like I would get exhausted, but
a french fry convention I could go there and
have all kinds of french fries.
Trog: True.
Gir: I would go with you.
I would absolutely go with you.
Wayne: It’d be great!
And there’s-and there are so many kinds
of fries.
There are so many things that you can do with
french fries that I think like, it’d be
a smaller scale convention, but you could
do it and it’d be awesome.
Like, you can get-you can get truffle fries,
you can get like fucking vinegar fries, you
can get fuckin’ poutine, you can get fuckin’
cheese fries—
Baaulp: It’s called poutine.
Gir: No, I want to go to the french fry convention
sponsored by Dr. Pepper.
[Trog laughs]
Wayne: And they would like-people would build
things out of french fries!
It would be crazy!
Log: There’s all kinds of crazy french fries
out there, there’s like-there’s like Tex-Mex
french fries, like carne asada fries—
Wayne: Oooh.
Log: There’s a place that I saw that served
uh, like tikka masala fries, like-just like
french fries with Indian curry ingredients.
That sounds crazy.
Gir: Have you ever had french fries with uh,
tzatziki?
Log: Nope.
Baaulp: Uh, probably at some point.
Gir: Pot-I mean it’s potatoes, so it goes
with fucking everything, that’s the thing,
that’s why fries are so good!
Log: But yeah, French Fry Convention.
Baaulp: You didn’t let me get my joke answer
out.
That was my serious answer.
I just want like, a serious like-not tournament,
like a fighting game convention of like, where
like, like-minded—Y’know.
Here’s—Let’s help each other get good.
We want to get good, right?
Let’s help each other get good.
My joke answer, though this still kind of
would be dope, uh, it kind of builds on Log’s
answer a little, FairCon.
Gir: A fair convention?
Baaulp: Yes, yes!
Here’s what it would be.
The real fair?
It sucks.
You go there for overpriced fair food and
like, there’s rip-offs at every turn, and
then there’s like-there’s like uh, a sprint
booth, where they try to sign you up for a
sprint thing, right?
Gir: Mhmm.
Baaulp: FairCon would be a con for people
who like going to the fair, and it would have
the amenities of a fair, but it’d be real.
It would just be rip-offs, so it’d be-it
would be—I’m imagining like, the show
floor would be like, the show floor would
be like, “Oh, yeah, check out all the fair
food, but at reasonable prices!”
And it’s like the best of, of all the fairs,
we’ve got the “best of” food of all
the fairs, like—
Gir: Baaulp, you’re just-you’re just describing
a fair, but with a lot of good rides and good
prices.
You want a fair that’s not ripping you off
[laughs].
Baaulp: No, no, there wouldn’t be rides.
There wouldn’t be rides, instead there’d
be panels about rides.
Gir: Well then—What?
That sounds like shit!
Trog: You would want to go to a room and listen
to people talk about a fair ride?
Gir: That sounds like shit!
Baaulp: Yeah!
Yeah, I-Yeah, I’d go to the, “I’ve seen
the world’s fattest pig,” panel, and when
they-when they were like—
Gir: That sounds awful!
Baaulp: Where they show you the world’s
fattest pig and you don’t have to pay the
dollar and they’re like, “Yeah, here it
is.
This is what they don’t want you to see.”
Gir: Now you’re describing a worse fair!
Baaulp: [Laughs] I think it’s good!
I think it’s good.
Gir: It’s a fair where you go to talk about,
“What if we were actually at the fair?
Wouldn’t that be great?”
Baaulp: I think it’s good.
Wayne: I can’t even-I can’t even hear
this.
French fry and pepper con, that’s all we
need.
Trog: I want a rhythm game convention.
Gir: Combine them!
French Fry and Pepper Con!
Wayne: We gotta stop—We’re getting into
dangerous territory, there will be consequences.
Baaulp: I still think my ideas would be a
good idea.
Trog: Um, yeah, I want a rhythm game convention,
that’s my answer.
But we should move on.
Wayne: That would actually be great, that
would be sick.
Gir: There’s no way that’s not real.
Trog: Not real right now, but.
Wayne: Not on a large scale.
Gir: No, not on a large scale, maybe, but
there’s probably like a local.
Trog: Yeah, it would be cool to have a rhythm
game convention that just has like, every
single good rhythm game playable, that’d
be fun.
Gir: That wouldn’t happen outside of America-I
mean outside of Japan, rather.
Trog: Yeah, exactly.
Um, I have another question.
Talking about fairs, this actually leads into
another question that I really like.
This is a question from TyeFyeDye, who says,
“If you had to design a Radio TV Solutions
themed amusement park, what rides would you
use to represent each member?”
I really like this question.
Wayne: This was one of the ones I was going
to go to, as well.
Um, but it’s tough, is the thing.
This is going to take some thinking.
Trog: Now, here’s the question.
Should we each design our own ride, or should
we each have to pick somebody else?
Baaulp: Yes, because I have such a good idea—Ohh,
that would be good, too.
Gir: I have a good idea for my ride.
Baaulp: How about one and one.
Design your own ride and then pick someone
else in the group to design a ride for.
Does that sound good?
Gir: I don’t have the brainpower for that.
Baaulp: I do.
Trog: I could do it.
But—
Baaulp: I’ll go first, fuck it!
My ride would be uh, it’s a small culinary
world.
It’d be a slow ride, basically we would
build an entire buffet restaurant, and the-the
slow ride goes through it, and the gimmick
is all the food is real and so you are able-the
ride goes slow enough that you are actively
encouraged to pick up plates of food and bring
them with you like out of the ride [laughs].
[Trog laughs]
Gir: You’re-you’re describing like the
inverse of those sushi bars with the rotating-the
rotating bar.
Trog: Yeah.
Gir: You’re moving and the food stays there.
Baaulp: And just like It’s a Small World,
it covers all the foods of the world, so you
start off maybe in North America—
Gir: Okay.
I’d ride that!
Baaulp: —and you’re like, “Oh, get some
brisket, we’re in Texas, get some brisket!”
And then, y’know, you eat your brisket and
then the next thing you know you’re in-you’re
in, y’know, you’re in uh, you’re in
China and it’s like—
Gir: Oh, we’re in Scotland, don’t touch
the fuckin’ haggis.
Baaulp: Yeah, yeah, yeah, and it’s-yeah,
and the gimmick is that all the food, it’s
not just a ride, all the food’s real, and
you’re actively like, you can’t get up,
but everything’s really low, so you’re
like encouraged to pick up plates of food
and eat it as you go [laughs].
Trog: It sounds like a health disaster, but
I do like the idea.
Gir: I’d be one of the first for the day.
Wayne: My ride would be-would take inspiration
off of one of my favorite amusement park rides,
uh, that I’ve ever—In regards to something
extra, it is one of my favorite amusement
park rides that I’ve ever been on.
So you ever-you ever been on those white water
rapids rides?
Not like the log flume, but it’s like-it’s
like a water ride where you go down a large
trail and you’re in like a big, circular
raft where you like look at each other and
like, you-you basically play the game of like,
“Okay, who’s gonna get the most wet,”
‘cause it’s kind of random, like you spin
and like you hit waves at certain points,
that shit’s fun.
But specifically, at the amusement park that
we would go to every year whenever we go up
to visit my grandma, um, the uh, they had
one of those rides, and along the ride, like
the ride would go along like the various walkways
in the park, and at various points there would
be a machine that you could put quarters into
and it was like a high pressure water gun
that you could blast people—
Gir: You can spray the people on the ride.
Wayne: Yeah, you spray the people on the ride.
So, my ride, would be like that, you’re
going through like a mountain and there’s
like, I guess there could be like Game Chimps
like, it’s like hot spring themed, so the
water’s hot and there could be like Game
Chimps all over it—
Gir: Oh!
Wayne: But the big twist?
The big twist?
Is that those guns not only can be operated
there, but they can be operated remotely,
and you could play the game, and we could
stream shooting at people with a water gun
on the ride, as they go—
[Trog laughs]
Gir: And they’re filled with bullets.
Trog: That’d be cool, yeah.
Wayne: No, no, not that.
[Gir laughs]
Log: Shooting hot water at people.
Trog: Yeah, I don’t know—I like that except
for the hot water, because all of my like,
mental images of theme parks are like, it’s
ninety degrees outside and my-and I’m miserable.
Gir: Yeah, you don’t really want a warm
water—
Trog: Right, right, yeah.
Wayne: It changes in the season, it changes
in the season.
Gir: Alright, warm water in the winter and
cold water in the summer, sure.
Wayne: Or maybe it’s hot like a hot tub
and then it gets cold at the end to cool you
off.
Gir: That would make you sick.
Trog: No.
Wayne: No.
Trog: It’d make you strong.
Gir: My ride would be fucking big, because
of the concept that I have.
Where y’know-y’know the thing where you
go in and you press against the wall and it
spins really fast so you’re pressed-the
gravity—
Baaulp: Uh-huh.
Trog: Mhmm.
Gir: Okay, imagine one big enough for just
two people, so it’s not super big, but it’s
big enough for two people, alright?
And it’s on a track, it’s on a moving
track, and then like, when whatever part of
the wall that you’re on isn’t-that you
aren’t—Whatever part of the wall that
you’re not on is a window so you can see
outside, right?
And it moves along this track and you have
like, a vision of like, it’s got some kind
of theme to it, I don’t care what the theme
is right now, but then it goes into a—
Trog: [Unintelligible]
Gir: …Sure, but then it goes into a dark
room, okay?
So you can’t see anything, and then I want
that ride, while you can’t see anything,
to start spinning so you’re pressed against
the wall, you can’t see shit, and then I
want it to be like uh, like uh, Space Odyssey-I
want it to just be like these bright lights
and these flashing lights while you’re spinning
really hard and you’re pressed against the
wall.
[Baaulp and Trog laugh]
Wayne: So you just want to give people seizures?
Gir: Well, you would have to sign a waiver.
Trog: You have to—Mhmm.
Gir: This is another thing where you have
to sign a waiver [laughs].
Trog: It’s a thrill ride!
It’s a thrill ride.
Wayne: Bro, your ideas seem to be like, they’re
damaging your fans.
Trog: Well, I like it.
Gir: Alright, so and then, y’know, you’re
pressed against the wall, the gravity’s
pulling you against the wall, you-the flashing
lights and colors, and then I want it to just
stop.
Wayne: So that’ll break people’s necks.
Trog: [Laughs] And then they just get flung
out of the ride and directly into the ambulance.
Wayne: If you stop and let the speed kill
normally—
Gir: I don’t mean literally like suddenly,
it’s just you hit the brakes.
Wayne: So you’re not engaging the brakes—
Gir: No, I’m not saying just hit the brakes.
Wayne: Okay, ‘cause that would act-absolutely
kill your beloved fans, they would die on
your ride.
Gir: I want the lights to just suddenly stop
and then it starts slowing down, and then
the ride ends.
Wayne: Y’know what you should do?
Do one of those spinning wall rides and like,
you-you put a rule up where it’s like, “You
can’t tell anyone what happens in this ride,”
and you go in, and like, as you’re spinning
it starts to slow down, and then all of a
sudden the floor drops out from under you
and you slide down into like, it’s like
funnel shaped, right?
So you don’t just drop and like, die and
hit the floor, you like slide down the wall
and you go to the next stage of the ride,
uh, as for what happens down there, I don’t
know, but—
Gir: Oh!
I just thought of the theming!
The theming of my ride is it’s-it’s [laughs]
It’s hoga-it’s Hogasm!
Trog: Oh god.
Wayne: [Laughs] That actually would be great.
Trog: How is that—That-that- you’re gonna
kill someone.
Gir: You start the ride and you hear, [in
a deep voice] “Oh, Santa?”
And then the moment—
Wayne: [In a deep voice] “We’ve come to—”
Gir: [In a deep voice] “We’ve come to—Hulk
Hogan, what are you doing here?”
And then the moment it goes [Gir imitates
a loud, distorted yell] that’s when the
lights turn off and you start spinning and
then the lights are flashing, and it’s just
this loud noise [laughs].
Baaulp: Wayne, when you said, “Oh, you’re
not supposed to tell people what you see on
this ride,” I thought it was gonna start
spinning and then you were going to project
something heinous in the middle [laughs].
Trog: [Laughs] You can’t tell anybody what
we’re showing you.
[Wayne laughs]
Trog: What’s yours, Log?
Log: Uh, I guess a-like a lazy river adventure.
Trog: Mhmm.
Log: So you can drift along, that’s fine,
but it would take-the river would take stops
in like various little constructs that are
like specifically for the lazy river, like
the lazy river’s the only way that leads
in and out, and so you can go into like-like
a cave or like a temple, or something, and
you can get out there and there’s like hot
tubs and little pools and stuff in there,
so you can go to the place that you like the
best, but you can also just continue on your
adventure.
Trog: I like that.
Sounds very relaxing.
Baaulp: Yeah!
It sounds like a good, nice time!
Trog: It’s a nice-nice little resort next
to-right next to MasterGir’s Hell Hogasm
ride.
Gir: Hogasm Hell!
Trog: You just can hear them screaming and
you can hear Hogasm being played at like,
2 decibels.
Baaulp: And Baaulp’s ride, where you’re
actively encouraged to get out of your seat
and get plates of food [laughs].
Trog: Yeah, um, mine kind of is like Gir’s,
uh, I-I like the idea that, of the y’know,
just ride that spins you around and around
like, so you’re stuck to the wall—
Gir: That’s my favorite kind!
Trog: But specifically, the gimmick of mine
would be that it is constantly playing music,
and the ride is always synced to the music,
and it’s constantly playing like, crazy
visuals in the center of the ride, and it’s
just, goin’ nuts.
And it’s specifically timed so that it works
with the tempo of the music, I think that
would be cool.
Baaulp: That’d be cool!
That’d be cool for a real ride, yeah!
Gir: I was gonna say, you can probably use
the rotation of the ride to do like a hologram
type thing.
Trog: Yeah, exactly.
So it’s like y’know, whenever you got
to a fair, every single ride is always just
playing this shitty techno or whatever, and
like—
Gir: Yeah.
Trog: That’s fun and all, but the ride is
never synced to the music, I want fair ride,
but it is one hundred percent synced to the
music, and also it’s playing good music
instead of bad music.
Gir: [In a pleading, country accent] “I
want good music in my fair!”
We had Nu Ma Nu Ma playing at my fair, once.
Baaulp: So, did we want to come up with a
ride for someone else?
Or did you want to move on?
Wayne: Scorpy’s ride is a-is a mirror maze
but with pressure plates that you can step
on that play extremely loud noises, like,
painfully loud noises.
Trog: Yeah, I think Scorpy definitely needs
a funhouse for sure in this fictional location.
Gir: Scorpy’s would be my ride except it’s
just you walk into a room and then get exposed
to loud noises.
Log: I think that Scorpy would have a haunted
house ride but the ride-but the track, the
little riding vehicle goes too fast to see
any of the monsters.
Gir: I was about to say the same thing!
It just goes too fast!
[Baaulp laughs]
Wayne: So you can’t get scared.
The first haunted house that can’t scare
you.
Trog: Scorpy has talked about how he likes
the like, on-rails haunted house rides, so,
I think he’d probably have one of those.
Wayne: Yeah.
Gir: I want the Video Tube.
Wayne: I also like the idea of the thing that
I said or like the on-rails like monster house
ride, but it’s connected to a mic that’s
extremely loud that he can just talk into
and talk at you whenever he wants.
Trog: Like he has to be there to operate this.
Wayne: Yeah.
He could do it remotely.
Gir: Guys, the collective crown jewel, the
collective crown jewel is the Video Tube.
Baaulp: Ohhhh.
Wayne: Oh, yeah!
Trog: Oh, yeah, a real life Video Tube, hell
yeah.
Gir: You go into the ride, and there’s like
a computer at the start of the ride, you load
up, max five videos—
Baaulp: You can search for any video on the
Internet!
Gir: Yeah, you load ‘em up, you get in the
ride, and then you go through-you do the Video
Tube with your videos, and then once the videos
are all done you get off, the next person
comes on, picks their videos.
Trog: I love that, because that’s really
sort of like a choose your own adventure-type
ride—
Gir: It is.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Trog: —where it could either be a nice,
relaxing ride, or it could be the worst thirty
minutes of your life.
Gir: Or just nightmare fuel.
Baaulp: Stinky Botte ten times!
Wayne: And if you’re not sure, we have a
preset list of videos to pick from uh, with
beautiful options such as, “Video Pizza,”
“Hebrew Clown with Babies,” uh, “will.i.am.
entertainment tonight song—”
Gir: You have a default set—
Trog: Uh, [burp sound effect] Factory.
Log: [Laughs] Noooo!
Wayne: Nooo.
[Gir laughs]
Wayne: That’s how we get a fucking arrest
warrant and the park gets closed down.
[Baaulp laughs]
Trog: We can’t disengage the locks on the
doors, we have four people stuck in there.
Wayne: You shouldn’t have even said that,
censor-censor what he said, because someone
will search on YouTube and find it and we
will be liable.
Baaulp: I’ll censor it, I will actually
censor what you said.
Trog: What?
No, the people have to know.
Wayne: You do not want to see [burp sound
effect] Factory.
Trog: Well now you’re going to have to censor
that, too.
Gir: Censor it by going [in a deep voice]
“Uh-oh.”
Wayne: Censor half of it.
Trog: [Laughs] Which half?
Nobody knows.
Gir: Yeah, just say [burp sound effect plays
once, then again].
Wayne: BEEP Factory.
Gir: No, I want just [burp sound effect].
Wayne: [Burp sound effect] blank, no that
sounds worse.
Trog: Yeah, you can’t, don’t make me sound
like a fucking freak, please.
Gir: Oh, [laughs] you’re right.
Wayne: Yeah, I mean—
Gir: Yeah, ‘cause you’re not a freak for
suggesting [burp sound effect] Factory!
Wayne: …I mean [laughs]—
[Baaulp laughs]
Wayne: We’re all freaks.
Gir: Oh, god.
Baaulp: Oh, fucking hell.
Wayne: Alright.
Baaulp: I think Wayne’s uh, ride would be
real quick, I think it’d be—
Gir: Wayne’s World.
Baaulp: They put you into giant—It’s like
bumper cars, but instead of bumper cars they
put you into giant, animatronic like-like
mech-gorilla mechs and you just have to beat
the shit out of each other.
Wayne: Like-like Rock ‘Em Sock ‘Em robots,
but you can do it-you get to play.
Yeah, that’d be a pretty dope arcade attraction,
you remember how when we went to the video
game museum they had like, giant Pong?
Like, imagine giant Rock ‘Em Sock ‘Em
robots where you like sat on either side and
controlled it, like that’d be pretty fun.
Gir: One-one last one, Erarg would have a
petting zoo but it’s exclusively dogs.
Baaulp: It’s just a dog zoo!
Gir: Yeah.
Trog: I would feel a little bad about charging
people for that, but y’know.
Gir: No, it’d be free.
You charge-you charge for treats.
Baaulp: Ohhh, yeahhh.
Gir: Like a real petting zoo.
A real petting zoo does that.
Wayne: Whose dogs are they?
Whose dogs are they?
Trog: They’re your dogs, Wayne.
It’s your amusement park.
You’ll have to take care of all these dogs.
Wayne: Okay [laughs].
Gir: We just bring our own dogs [laughs]!
Baaulp: Honestly, I’d go to a dog zoo, just,
“Hey, we got one of every dog!”
Gir: That’s a lot of dogs!
Wayne: As long as they’re well taken care
of.
Trog: That’s a lot of dogs.
Wayne: It’s kind of just a shelter, at that
point.
Gir: You can let them adopt them!
Have the local shelter supply dogs!
Wayne: We didn’t know where we’d begin,
but we know how we’re wrapping it up, at
least I do.
Baaulp: Peppers.
Gir: With peppers.
Wayne: Thank you for listening, if you have
questions for the next episode, please join
the WayneRadioTV Discord and look for the
podcast questions channel.
Make sure you ask good questions that aren’t
jokes, they can be funny, but don’t try.
Or—
Gir: Don’t try.
Wayne: It’s a complicated subject.
Go to discord.gg/WayneRadioTV if you want
to see my streams and the group’s, twitch.tv/wayneradiotv,
we’re all up in there on times, and we all
stream these days.
Plug yourselves!
[Log yawns]
Gir: Trog, you first.
Wayne: Log’s too tired, Log need a nappy.
Log: I do.
Trog: Yeah, I’m on Twitch sometimes, twitch.tv/tr0g,
um, only other thing I have to plug will have
already happened by the time this goes up,
so—
Baaulp: Uh-huh, yeah.
Trog: I hope you enjoyed the Funny Rave and
uh, I’m sure it was great, even though it
hasn’t happened yet for me, but it has happened
for you.
Baaulp: But it will happen for you, yes, you
better have tuned in.
Trog: Yeah, so watch it.
Baaulp: If not, uh, look it up.
Gir: Sorry, I’m going to be busy, I assume.
Wayne: I’ll be watching.
Baaulp: I am Baaulp—
Gir: Hi.
Baaulp: Look for me on Twitch—
Wayne: Oh, we’re doing intros, I thought
this was the outro.
[Baaulp scoffs]
[Gir laughs]
Wayne: I am Wayne [laughs].
Baaulp: Look for Baaulp, B-A-A-U-L-P on YouTube,
Twitch, Twitter, check it out!
I made videos, go watch Launch Test!
Wayne: Please watch Launch Test.
Gir: MasterGir, Twitch, Twitter, Youtube.
Wayne: You just have a website you can link
to, BigWarp, right?
Gir: Yeah, bigwarp.com has all the links to
all my shit.
Wayne: I promote my-I promote be friends better
than they promote themselves.
Gir: I forget about it.
Wayne: [Laughs] Logmore.
Log: [Sighs] twitch.tv/logmore, twitter.com/logblaster,
but—
Wayne: Promo code: Gather Ye Power.
Log: Yeah, you can Google Gather Ye Power
and get straight to the business of it.
Take one back.
Wayne: Get a free comic by Googling promo
code, “Gather Ye Power.”
Baaulp: Oh my god, you don’t have to pay?
Holy shit!
Wayne: Yeah, it’s free comics!
Log: No pay.
Baaulp: Wow.
Gir: I thought Baaulp was about to be like,
“Oh my god, you don’t have to promote
him!”
Wayne: Anyways, now that the podcast is all
wrapped up, you guys wanna play Peppers?
Baaulp: Hell yeah!
Alright, let me see what I got.
Wayne: Alright I’m going-I’m going first.
I get first dibs, I get first dibs.
Baaulp: Okay, okay, okay.
[Wayne inhales]
[Biting sound effect plays]
Wayne, panting: Ah!
Hot.
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
Log: You’re not supposed to eat them yet.
Wayne: What?
What was I s’posed to do?
Trog: You’ve broken the first rule of Peppers.
Log: You have to toss it in the air and then
pick up the seeds.
Wayne: Well I already ate it.
Log: Well, I guess we can’t play anymore.
[Puff of air sound effect plays]
Gir: Oh!
My-my pepper released a noxious gas!
What do I do?
Log: Alright, Let-let’s [sighs] I’ll get
my wireless pepper.
It’s got a bit of delay, but we can try
it.
Wayne: Wave pepper [laughs].
[Baaulp laughs]
Log: Make sure to set it to channel 3.
Wayne: Bro, did you cat pee on this pepper?
This shit’s gross!
Baaulp: I’m sorry, I’m sorry, the only
one we got is this Mad Catz uh, Fresno Frenzy
pepper, um, sorry.
[Wayne and Gir laugh]
Trog: Buddy, it’s a little sticky, but it
works.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Gir: Yeah, my-my little brother chewed on
the stem.
Wayne: New pepper hybrid, the Fresno Frenzy
pepper, coming to you soon, official RadioTVSolutions
pepper, goodnight!